<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<metadata id="MPP1285_21-51-02-04-1">
  <file family="145" manual="AMM" pn="1285" chg="R" tsn="55" is_tr="false">
    <title>AMM PART II-1285 - CHAPTER 21-51-02-04 - DUAL HEAT EXCHANGER - REMOVAL/INSTALLATION</title>
    <path>/CHAPTER_21</path>
    <hash>022073522f56e211750467089782bf7d</hash>
  </file>
  <pages>
    <page number="1" width="216.0" height="279.0">
      <data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL DUAL HEAT EXCHANGER - REMOVAL/INSTALLATION EFFECTIVITY: ALL 1. General A. This section gives the procedures to remove and install the dual heat exchangers of the cooling pack system. B. These procedures are applicable to the LH and RH dual heat exchangers. C. The LH dual heat exchanger is installed on the LH side of the forward lower fairing. D. The RH dual heat exchanger is installed on the RH side of the forward lower fairing. E. The procedures in this section are given in the sequence below. The tasks identified with ( &#x2666;) are part of the Scheduled Maintenance Requirements Document (SMRD). TASK NUMBER DESCRIPTION EFFECTIVITY ALL 21-51-02-000-801-A DUAL HEAT EXCHANGER - REMOVAL   DUAL HEAT EXCHANGER - INSTALLA- ALL 21-51-02-400-801-A TION  EMB-145  - AMM 1285 General 21-51-02 Page 1 of 10 Rev 48 - Oct 30/15 Copyright © by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
    </page>
    <page number="2" width="216.0" height="279.0">
      <data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL TASK 21-51-02-000-801-A EFFECTIVITY: ALL 2. DUAL HEAT EXCHANGER - REMOVAL A. General (1) This task gives the instructions to remove the dual heat exchanger. B. References REFERENCE DESIGNATION AMM MPP 06-41-01/100 - C. Zones and Accesses ZONE PANEL/DOOR LOCATION 191 191EL LH side of the forward lower fairing 191 191FR RH side of the forward lower fairing 191 191GL Bottom of the forward lower fairing D. Tools and Equipment ITEM DESCRIPTION PURPOSE QTY Sharp plastic  To remove the flange seal 1 spatula. E. Auxiliary Items Not Applicable F. Consumable Materials SPECIFICATION DESCRIPTION QTY (BRAND) Isopropyl alcohol (TT-I-735) AR G. Expandable Parts Not Applicable H. Persons Recommended QTY FUNCTION PLACE 1 Does the task LH or RH side of the forward lower fairing 1 Helps the other technician LH or RH side of the forward lower fairing I. Preparation SUBTASK 841-002-A (1) On the Circuit Breaker Panel, open the PACK 1 and PACK 2 circuit breakers and attach a DO-NOT-CLOSE tag to them. EMB-145  - AMM 1285 000-801-A/400 21-51-02 Page 2 of 10 Rev 55 - Oct 29/18 Copyright © by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
    </page>
    <page number="3" width="216.0" height="279.0">
      <data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL (2) Remove access panels as applicable: &#x2022; 191EL or 191FR (AMM MPP 06-41-01/100). &#x2022; 191GL (AMM MPP 06-41-01/100). J. Removal (Figure 401)  SUBTASK 020-002-A (1) Loosen the clamps (9), (10), (11) and (23) to disconnect the tubes (16), (17), (18) and (19) from the dual heat exchanger (1). (2) Loosen the clamp (21) to disconnect the rubber connection (20) from the dual temperature control valve. (3) Loosen the clamp (7) to disconnect the outlet grate (6) from the duct (8). (4) Remove the screws (5) (10 positions) and then remove the outlet grate (6). (5) Get