<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata id="025-MPP1285_05-TOC">
	<file family="145" manual="AMM" pn="1285" chg="R" tsn="55" is_tr="false">
		<title>AMM PART II-1285 - CHAPTER 05 - TABLE OF CONTENTS</title>
		<path>/CHAPTER_05</path>
		<hash>18474a0f884088adb95563b613f3e0bd</hash>
	</file>
	<pages>
		<page number="1" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL TABLE OF CONTENTS PAGEBLOCK REVISION REVISION TASK STATUS DATE 05-00-00/200 U Oct 30/15 TIME LIMITS - MAINTENANCE PRACTICES   05-20-01/600 U Oct 30/15 FORWARD FUSELAGE I - RADOME - EXTERNAL - INSPECTION/    CHECK 05-20-01-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 FORWARD FUSELAGE I - RADOME - EXTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL    INSPECTION 05-20-02/600 U Oct 30/15 FORWARD FUSELAGE I - RADOME - INTERNAL - INSPECTION/   CHECK 05-20-02-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 FORWARD FUSELAGE I - RADOME - INTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL   INSPECTION 05-20-03/600 U Oct 30/15 FORWARD FUSELAGE I LH/RH SIDES - EXTERNAL - INSPECTION/   CHECK 05-20-03-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 FORWARD FUSELAGE I LH/RH SIDES - EXTERNAL GENERAL VISU-   AL INSPECTION 05-20-04/600 U Oct 30/15 FORWARD FUSELAGE I LH/RH SIDES - INTERNAL - INSPECTION/   CHECK 05-20-04-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 FORWARD FUSELAGE I LH SIDE - INTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL IN-    SPECTION 05-20-05/600 U Oct 30/15 FORWARD FUSELAGE I RH SIDE - INTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK    05-20-05-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 FORWARD FUSELAGE I RH SIDE - INTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL IN-   SPECTION Revision Status: U - Unchanged, R - Revised, N - New, D - Deleted EMB-145  - AMM 1285 Chapter 05 TOC Page 1 of 32 Rev 55 - Oct 29/18 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="2" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL PAGEBLOCK REVISION REVISION TASK STATUS DATE 05-20-06/600 U Oct 30/15 FORWARD FUSELAGE I - ELECTRONIC COMPARTMENT - EXTERNAL   - INSPECTION/CHECK 05-20-06-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 FORWARD FUSELAGE I - ELECTRONIC COMPARTMENT - EXTER-   NAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-07/600 U Oct 30/15 FORWARD FUSELAGE I - ELECTRONIC COMPARTMENT - INTERNAL    - INSPECTION/CHECK 05-20-07-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 NLG &amp; FWD ELECTRONIC COMPARTMENTS / FWD PRESSURE    BULKHEAD UPPER SIDE - INTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPEC- TION 05-20-10/600 U Apr 29/16 FORWARD FUSELAGE II - COCKPIT BOTTOM - EXTERNAL - INSPEC-   TION/CHECK 05-20-10-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 FORWARD FUSELAGE II - COCKPIT BOTTOM - EXTERNAL GENER-   AL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-11/600 U Oct 30/15 FORWARD FUSELAGE II - COCKPIT BOTTOM - INTERNAL - INSPEC-   TION/CHECK 05-20-11-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 FORWARD FUSELAGE II - COCKPIT BOTTOM - INTERNAL GENER-   AL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-13/600 U Oct 30/15 FORWARD FUSELAGE II - COCKPIT LH/RH SIDES - EXTERNAL - IN-   SPECTION/CHECK 05-20-13-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 FORWARD FUSELAGE II - COCKPIT LH/RH SIDES - EXTERNAL    GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-14/600 U Oct 30/15 FORWARD FUSELAGE II - COCKPIT LH/RH SIDES - INTERNAL - IN-    SPECTION/CHECK Revision Status: U - Unchanged, R - Revised, N - New, D - Deleted EMB-145  - AMM 1285 Chapter 05 TOC Page 2 of 32 Rev 55 - Oct 29/18 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="3" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL PAGEBLOCK REVISION REVISION TASK STATUS DATE 05-20-14-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 FORWARD FUSELAGE II - COCKPIT LH/RH SIDES - INTERNAL GEN-   ERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-15/600 U Oct 30/15 FORWARD FUSELAGE II - COCKPIT TOP - EXTERNAL - INSPECTION/   CHECK 05-20-15-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 FORWARD FUSELAGE II - COCKPIT TOP - EXTERNAL GENERAL    VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-16/600 U Oct 30/15 FORWARD FUSELAGE II - COCKPIT TOP - INTERNAL - INSPECTION/    CHECK 05-20-16-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 FORWARD FUSELAGE II - COCKPIT TOP - INTERNAL GENERAL   VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-17/600 U Oct 30/15 CENTER FUSELAGE I - PASSENGER CABIN BOTTOM - EXTERNAL -   INSPECTION/CHECK 05-20-17-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 CENTER FUSELAGE I - PASSENGER CABIN BOTTOM - EXTERNAL   GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-18/600 CONFIG-1 U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: ACFT MODEL(S) EMB-145   CENTER FUSELAGE I - PASSENGER CABIN BOTTOM - INTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK 05-20-18-200-801-A CONFIG-1 U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: ACFT MODEL(S) EMB-145   CENTER FUSELAGE I - PASSENGER CABIN BOTTOM - INTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-18/600 CONFIG-2 U Apr 28/17 EFFECTIVITY: ACFT MODEL(S) EMB-135    CENTER FUSELAGE I - PASSENGER CABIN BOTTOM - INTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK 05-20-18-200-801-A CONFIG-2 U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: ACFT MODEL(S) EMB-135    CENTER FUSELAGE I - PASSENGER CABIN BOTTOM - INTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION Revision Status: U - Unchanged, R - Revised, N - New, D - Deleted EMB-145  - AMM 1285 Chapter 05 TOC Page 3 of 32 Rev 55 - Oct 29/18 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="4" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL PAGEBLOCK REVISION REVISION TASK STATUS DATE 05-20-19/600 U Oct 30/15 CENTER FUSELAGE I - PASSENGER CABIN TOP - EXTERNAL - IN-   SPECTION/CHECK 05-20-19-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 CENTER FUSELAGE I - PASSENGER CABIN TOP - EXTERNAL GEN-   ERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-20/600 U Oct 30/15 CENTER FUSELAGE I - PASSENGER CABIN TOP - INTERNAL - IN-    SPECTION/CHECK 05-20-20-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 CENTER FUSELAGE I - PASSENGER CABIN TOP - INTERNAL GEN-    ERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-21/600 U Oct 30/15 CENTER FUSELAGE II - PASSENGER CABIN BOTTOM - EXTERNAL -   INSPECTION/CHECK 05-20-21-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 CENTER FUSELAGE II - PASSENGER CABIN BOTTOM - EXTERNAL   GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-22/600 CONFIG-1 U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: ACFT MODEL(S) EMB-145   CENTER FUSELAGE II - PASSENGER CABIN BOTTOM - INTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK 05-20-22-200-801-A CONFIG-1 U Apr 29/16 EFFECTIVITY: ACFT MODEL(S) EMB-145   CENTER FUSELAGE II - PASSENGER CABIN BOTTOM - INTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-22/600 CONFIG-2 U Apr 28/17 EFFECTIVITY: ACFT MODEL(S) EMB-135   CENTER FUSELAGE II - PASSENGER CABIN BOTTOM - INTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK 05-20-22-200-801-A CONFIG-2 U Oct 31/16 EFFECTIVITY: ACFT MODEL(S) EMB-135    CENTER FUSELAGE II - PASSENGER CABIN BOTTOM - INTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION Revision Status: U - Unchanged, R - Revised, N - New, D - Deleted EMB-145  - AMM 1285 Chapter 05 TOC Page 4 of 32 Rev 55 - Oct 29/18 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="5" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL PAGEBLOCK REVISION REVISION TASK STATUS DATE 05-20-23/600 U Oct 30/15 CENTER FUSELAGE II - PASSENGER CABIN LH/RH SIDES - EXTER-   NAL - INSPECTION/CHECK 05-20-23-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 CENTER FUSELAGE II - PASSENGER CABIN LH/RH SIDES - EXTER-   NAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-23-200-802-A U Oct 30/15 CENTER FUSELAGE II - PASSENGER CABIN WINDOWS AERODY-    NAMIC SEALING - EXTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-24/600 U Oct 30/15 CENTER FUSELAGE II - PASSENGER CABIN LH/RH SIDES - INTER-    NAL - INSPECTION/CHECK 05-20-24-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 CENTER FUSELAGE II - PASSENGER CABIN LH/RH SIDES - INTER-   NAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-25/600 CONFIG-1 U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: ACFT MODEL(S) EMB-145   CENTER FUSELAGE II - PASSENGER CABIN TOP - INTERNAL - IN- SPECTION/CHECK 05-20-25-200-801-A CONFIG-1 U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: ACFT MODEL(S) EMB-145   CENTER FUSELAGE II - PASSENGER CABIN TOP - INTERNAL GEN- ERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-25/600 CONFIG-2 U Apr 28/17 EFFECTIVITY: ACFT MODEL(S) EMB-135   CENTER FUSELAGE II - PASSENGER CABIN TOP - INTERNAL - IN- SPECTION/CHECK 05-20-25-200-801-A CONFIG-2 U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: ACFT MODEL(S) EMB-135   CENTER FUSELAGE II - PASSENGER CABIN TOP - INTERNAL GEN- ERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-26/600 U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: EMB-145ER/EP/EU AND EMB-135ER MODELS OR    EMB-145/ER/EP/EU AND EMB-135ER MODELS PASSENGER CABIN BOTTON FOR ER/EP/EU MODELS - INSPECTION/ CHECK Revision Status: U - Unchanged, R - Revised, N - New, D - Deleted EMB-145  - AMM 1285 Chapter 05 TOC Page 5 of 32 Rev 55 - Oct 29/18 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="6" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL PAGEBLOCK REVISION REVISION TASK STATUS DATE 05-20-26-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: EMB-145ER/EP/EU AND EMB-135ER MODELS OR   EMB-145/ER/EP/EU AND EMB-135ER MODELS CENTER FUSELAGE III - PASSENGER CABIN BOTTOM - EXTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-26-200-805-A U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: EMB-145ER/EP/EU AND EMB-135ER MODELS    WING-TO-FUSELAGE FAIRING - INTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL IN- SPECTION 05-20-27/600 U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: EMB-145ER/EP/EU AND EMB-135ER MODELS    PASSENGER CABIN BOTTON FOR ER/EP/EU MODELS - INSPECTION/ CHECK 05-20-27-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: EMB-145ER/EP/EU AND EMB-135ER MODELS   CENTER FUSELAGE III - PASSENGER CABIN BOTTOM - INTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-27-200-802-A U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: EMB-145ER/EP/EU AND EMB-135ER MODELS   CENTER FUSELAGE III - WING STUB - INTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-28/600 U Oct 30/15 CENTER FUSELAGE I - PASSENGER CABIN LH/RH SIDES - INTERNAL   - INSPECTION/CHECK 05-20-28-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 CENTER FUSELAGE I - PASSENGER CABIN LH/RH SIDES - INTER-   NAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-29/600 U Oct 30/15 CENTER FUSELAGE III - PASSENGER CABIN LH/RH SIDES - EXTER-   NAL - INSPECTION/CHECK 05-20-29-200-802-A U Oct 30/15 CENTER FUSELAGE III - PASSENGER CABIN LH/RH SIDES - EX-    TERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-30/600 U Oct 30/15 CENTER FUSELAGE III - PASSENGER CABIN LH/RH SIDES - INTER-    NAL - INSPECTION/CHECK Revision Status: U - Unchanged, R - Revised, N - New, D - Deleted EMB-145  - AMM 1285 Chapter 05 TOC Page 6 of 32 Rev 55 - Oct 29/18 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="7" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL PAGEBLOCK REVISION REVISION TASK STATUS DATE 05-20-30-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 CENTER FUSELAGE III - PASSENGER CABIN LH/RH SIDES - INTER-   NAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-31/600 U Oct 30/15 CENTER FUSELAGE III - PASSENGER CABIN TOP - EXTERNAL - IN-   SPECTION/CHECK 05-20-31-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 CENTER FUSELAGE III - PASSENGER CABIN TOP - EXTERNAL    GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-32/600 CONFIG-1 U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: ACFT MODEL(S) EMB-145    CENTER FUSELAGE III - PASSENGER CABIN TOP - INTERNAL - IN- SPECTION/CHECK 05-20-32-200-801-A CONFIG-1 U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: ACFT MODEL(S) EMB-145   CENTER FUSELAGE III - PASSENGER CABIN TOP - INTERNAL GEN- ERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-32/600 CONFIG-2 U Apr 28/17 EFFECTIVITY: ACFT MODEL(S) EMB-135   CENTER FUSELAGE III - PASSENGER CABIN TOP - INTERNAL - IN- SPECTION/CHECK 05-20-32-200-801-A CONFIG-2 U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: ACFT MODEL(S) EMB-135   CENTER FUSELAGE III - PASSENGER CABIN TOP - INTERNAL GEN- ERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-33/600 U Oct 30/15 CENTER FUSELAGE IV - PASSENGER CABIN BOTTOM - EXTERNAL -   INSPECTION/CHECK 05-20-33-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 CENTER FUSELAGE IV - PASSENGER CABIN BOTTOM - EXTERNAL   GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-34/600 CONFIG-1 U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: ACFT MODEL(S) EMB-145    CENTER FUSELAGE IV - PASSENGER CABIN BOTTOM - INTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK Revision Status: U - Unchanged, R - Revised, N - New, D - Deleted EMB-145  - AMM 1285 Chapter 05 TOC Page 7 of 32 Rev 55 - Oct 29/18 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="8" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL PAGEBLOCK REVISION REVISION TASK STATUS DATE 05-20-34-200-801-A CONFIG-1 U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: ACFT MODEL(S) EMB-145   CENTER FUSELAGE IV - PASSENGER CABIN BOTTOM - INTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-34/600 CONFIG-2 U Apr 28/17 EFFECTIVITY: ACFT MODEL(S) EMB-135   CENTER FUSELAGE IV - PASSENGER CABIN BOTTOM - INTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK 05-20-34-200-801-A CONFIG-2 U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: ACFT MODEL(S) EMB-135    CENTER FUSELAGE IV - PASSENGER CABIN BOTTOM - INTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-35/600 U Oct 30/15 CENTER FUSELAGE IV - PASSENGER CABIN LH/RH SIDES - EXTER-    NAL - INSPECTION/CHECK 05-20-35-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 CENTER FUSELAGE IV - PASSENGER CABIN LH/RH SIDES - EX-   TERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-36/600 U Oct 30/15 CENTER FUSELAGE IV - PASSENGER CABIN WINDOWS - EXTERNAL   - INSPECTION/CHECK 05-20-36-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 CENTER FUSELAGE IV - PASSENGER CABIN WINDOWS AERODY-   NAMIC SEALING- EXTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-37/600 U Oct 30/15 CENTER FUSELAGE IV - PASSENGER CABIN LH/RH SIDES - INTER-   NAL - INSPECTION/CHECK 05-20-37-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 CENTER FUSELAGE IV - PASSENGER CABIN LH/RH SIDES - INTER-   NAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-38/600 U Oct 30/15 REAR FUSELAGE I - BAGGAGE COMPARTMENT BOTTOM - EXTER-    NAL - INSPECTION/CHECK 05-20-38-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 REAR FUSELAGE I - BAGGAGE COMPARTMENT BOTTOM - EXTER-    NAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION Revision Status: U - Unchanged, R - Revised, N - New, D - Deleted EMB-145  - AMM 1285 Chapter 05 TOC Page 8 of 32 Rev 55 - Oct 29/18 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="9" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL PAGEBLOCK REVISION REVISION TASK STATUS DATE 05-20-39/600 U Oct 30/15 REAR FUSELAGE I - BAGGAGE COMPARTMENT BOTTOM - INTER-   NAL - INSPECTION/CHECK 05-20-39-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 REAR FUSELAGE I - BAGGAGE COMPARTMENT BOTTOM - INTER-   NAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-40/600 U Oct 30/15 REAR FUSELAGE I - BAGGAGE COMPARTMENT LH/RH SIDES - EX-    TERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK 05-20-40-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 REAR FUSELAGE I - BAGGAGE COMPARTMENT LH/RH SIDES - EX-    TERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-41/600 U Oct 30/15 PRESSURE BULKHEAD AND BAGGAGE COMPARTMENT LH/RH   SIDES - INTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK 05-20-41-200-801-A U Apr 29/16 PRESSURE BULKHEAD - PRESSURIZED AREA SIDE - INTERNAL   GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-42/600 U Oct 30/15 REAR FUSELAGE I - BAGGAGE COMPARTMENT LH/RH SIDES - IN-   TERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK 05-20-42-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 REAR FUSELAGE I - BAGGAGE COMPARTMENT LH/RH SIDES - IN-   TERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-44/600 U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: CLASS-C BAGGAGE COMPARTMENT   REAR FUSELAGE I - BAGGAGE COMPARTMENT TOP - CLASS C - IN- TERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK 05-20-44-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: CLASS-C BAGGAGE COMPARTMENT    REAR FUSELAGE I - BAGGAGE COMPARTMENT TOP - CLASS C - INTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-45/600 U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: CLASS-D BAGGAGE COMPARTMENT    REAR FUSELAGE I - BAGGAGE COMPARTMENT TOP - INTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK Revision Status: U - Unchanged, R - Revised, N - New, D - Deleted EMB-145  - AMM 1285 Chapter 05 TOC Page 9 of 32 Rev 55 - Oct 29/18 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="10" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL PAGEBLOCK REVISION REVISION TASK STATUS DATE 05-20-45-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: CLASS-D BAGGAGE COMPARTMENT   REAR FUSELAGE I - BAGGAGE COMPARTMENT TOP - INTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-46/600 U Apr 29/16 REAR FUSELAGE II - AFT OF REAR PRESSURE BULKHEAD - EXTER-   NAL - INSPECTION/CHECK 05-20-46-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 REAR FUSELAGE II - AFT OF REAR PRESSURE BULKHEAD - EX-    TERNAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-47/600 U Oct 30/15 REAR FUSELAGE II - AFT OF REAR PRESSURE BULKHEAD - INTER-    NAL - INSPECTION/CHECK 05-20-47-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 REAR FUSELAGE II - AFT OF REAR PRESSURE BULKHEAD - IN-   TERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-48/600 U Oct 30/15 RUDDER I AND RUDDER II - EXTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK   05-20-48-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 RUDDER I AND RUDDER II - EXTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPEC-   TION 05-20-49/600 U Oct 30/15 RUDDER I AND II - INTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK   05-20-49-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 RUDDER I AND II - INTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION   05-20-50/600 U Oct 30/15 RUDDER II - EXTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK    05-20-50-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 RUDDER II - EXTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION    05-20-52/600 U Oct 30/15 HORIZONTAL STABILIZER - EXTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK   05-20-52-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 HORIZONTAL STABILIZER - EXTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPEC-   TION Revision Status: U - Unchanged, R - Revised, N - New, D - Deleted EMB-145  - AMM 1285 Chapter 05 TOC Page 10 of 32 Rev 55 - Oct 29/18 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="11" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL PAGEBLOCK REVISION REVISION TASK STATUS DATE 05-20-53/600 U Oct 30/15 HORIZONTAL STABILIZER - INTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK   05-20-53-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 HORIZONTAL STABILIZER - INTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPEC-   TION 05-20-56/600 U Oct 30/15 REAR FUSELAGE II - TAIL CONE FAIRING - EXTERNAL - INSPEC-    TION/CHECK 05-20-56-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 REAR FUSELAGE II - TAIL CONE FAIRING - EXTERNAL GENERAL    VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-57/600 U Oct 30/15 REAR FUSELAGE II - TAIL CONE FAIRING - INTERNAL - INSPECTION/   CHECK 05-20-57-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 REAR FUSELAGE II - TAIL CONE FAIRING - INTERNAL GENERAL   VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-58/600 U Oct 30/15 VERTICAL STABILIZER - EXTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK   05-20-58-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 VERTICAL STABILIZER - EXTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPEC-   TION 05-20-58-200-803-A U Apr 27/18 VERTICAL STABILIZER AND RUDDERS - EXTERNAL GENERAL VIS-   UAL INSPECTION 05-20-59/600 U Oct 30/15 VERTICAL STABILIZER - INTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK    05-20-59-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 VERTICAL STABILIZER - AREA BETWEEN SPARS I/II AND II/III- IN-    TERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-62/600 U Oct 30/15 ELEVATOR - EXTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK   05-20-62-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 ELEVATOR - EXTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION   Revision Status: U - Unchanged, R - Revised, N - New, D - Deleted EMB-145  - AMM 1285 Chapter 05 TOC Page 11 of 32 Rev 55 - Oct 29/18 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="12" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL PAGEBLOCK REVISION REVISION TASK STATUS DATE 05-20-63/600 U Oct 30/15 ELEVATOR - INTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK   05-20-63-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 ELEVATOR - INTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION   05-20-64/600 U Oct 30/15 HORIZONTAL STABILIZER TO VERTICAL STABILIZER ATTACHMENT -    EXTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK 05-20-64-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 HORIZONTAL STABILIZER TO VERTICAL STABILIZER ATTACH-    MENT - EXTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-65/600 U Oct 30/15 HORIZONTAL STABILIZER TO VERTICAL STABILIZER ATTACHMENT -   INTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK 05-20-65-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 HORIZONTAL STABILIZER TO VERTICAL STABILIZER ATTACH-   MENT - INTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-65-200-803-A U Oct 30/15 EMPENNAGE - VERTICAL STABILIZER FAIRINGS DORSAL FIN   LEADING EDGE AND STABILIZER ATTACHMENT TO TAIL FIN - IN- TERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-66/600 U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: EMB-145LR/LU/MR/MP/MK AND EMB-135LR/KE/KL MOD-   ELS PASSENGER CABIN BOTTON - EXTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK 05-20-66-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: EMB-145LR/LU/MR/MP/MK AND EMB-135LR/KE/KL   MODELS CENTER FUSELAGE III - PASSENGER CABIN BOTTOM - EXTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-67/600 CONFIG-1 U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: EMB-145LR/LU/MR/MP/MK AND EMB-135LR/KE/KL MOD-    ELS PASSENGER CABIN BOTTON - INTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK Revision Status: U - Unchanged, R - Revised, N - New, D - Deleted EMB-145  - AMM 1285 Chapter 05 TOC Page 12 of 32 Rev 55 - Oct 29/18 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="13" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL PAGEBLOCK REVISION REVISION TASK STATUS DATE 05-20-67-200-801-A CONFIG-1 U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: EMB-145LR/LU/MR/MP/MK AND EMB-135LR/KE/KL   MODELS CENTER FUSELAGE III - PASSENGER CABIN BOTTOM - INTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-67/600 CONFIG-2 U Apr 28/17 EFFECTIVITY: EMB-145LR/LU/MR/MP/MK AND EMB-135LR/KE/KL MOD-   ELS PASSENGER CABIN BOTTON - INTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK 05-20-67-200-801-A CONFIG-2 U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: EMB-145LR/LU/MR/MP/MK AND EMB-135LR/KE/KL    MODELS CENTER FUSELAGE III - PASSENGER CABIN BOTTOM - INTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-70/600 U Oct 30/15 COWLING - EXTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK    05-20-70-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 COWLING - EXTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION   05-20-71/600 U Oct 30/15 COWLING - INTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK   05-20-71-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 COWLING - INTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION   05-20-72/600 U Oct 30/15 PYLON - EXTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK   05-20-72-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 PYLONS - EXTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION   05-20-73/600 U Oct 30/15 PYLON - INTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK    05-20-73-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 PYLONS - INTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION    05-20-74/600 U Oct 30/15 THRUST REVERSER MODULE - EXTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK   Revision Status: U - Unchanged, R - Revised, N - New, D - Deleted EMB-145  - AMM 1285 Chapter 05 TOC Page 13 of 32 Rev 55 - Oct 29/18 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="14" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL PAGEBLOCK REVISION REVISION TASK STATUS DATE 05-20-74-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 THRUST REVERSER MODULE - EXTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL IN-   SPECTION 05-20-75/600 U Oct 30/15 THRUST REVERSER MODULE - INTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK   05-20-75-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 THRUST REVERSER MODULE - INTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL IN-    SPECTION 05-20-76/600 U Oct 30/15 WING LEADING EDGE - INSPECTION/CHECK    05-20-76-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 WING LEADING EDGE - EXTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION   05-20-77/600 U Oct 30/15 INBOARD WING LEADING EDGE - INTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK   05-20-77-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 WING LEADING EDGE - INTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION   05-20-78/600 U Oct 30/15 WING LEADING EDGE II - INSPECTION/CHECK   05-20-78-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 WING LEADING EDGE II - EXTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPEC-   TION 05-20-79/600 U Oct 30/15 CENTER FUSELAGE I - PASSENGER CABIN LH/RH SIDES - EXTER-    NAL - INSPECTION/CHECK 05-20-79-200-802-A U Oct 30/15 CENTER FUSELAGE I - PASSENGER-CABIN-WINDOWS AERODY-    NAMIC SEALING- EXTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-79-200-803-A U Oct 30/15 CENTER FUSELAGE I - PASSENGER CABIN LH/RH SIDES - EXTER-   NAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-80/600 U Oct 30/15 WING LEADING EDGE III - INSPECTION/CHECK   Revision Status: U - Unchanged, R - Revised, N - New, D - Deleted EMB-145  - AMM 1285 Chapter 05 TOC Page 14 of 32 Rev 55 - Oct 29/18 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="15" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL PAGEBLOCK REVISION REVISION TASK STATUS DATE 05-20-80-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 WING LEADING EDGE III - EXTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPEC-   TION 05-20-81/600 U Oct 30/15 OUTBOARD WING LEADING EDGE - INTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK   05-20-81-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 OUTBOARD WING LEADING EDGE - INTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL    INSPECTION 05-20-82/600 U Oct 30/15 WING ROOT SECTION BETWEEN SPAR I AND SPAR II - EXTERNAL -    INSPECTION/CHECK 05-20-82-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 WING ROOT SECTION BETWEEN SPAR I AND SPAR II - EXTERNAL   GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-83/600 U Oct 30/15 WING ROOT SECTION BETWEEN SPAR I AND SPAR II - INTERNAL -   INSPECTION/CHECK 05-20-83-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 WING ROOT SECTION BETWEEN SPAR I AND SPAR II - INTERNAL   GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-84/600 U Oct 30/15 WING ROOT SECTION BETWEEN SPAR II AND SPAR III - EXTERNAL -   INSPECTION/CHECK 05-20-84-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 WING - EXTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION   05-20-85/600 U Oct 30/15 WING ROOT SECTION BETWEEN SPAR II AND SPAR III - INTERNAL -    INSPECTION/CHECK 05-20-85-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 WING - INTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION    05-20-86/600 U Oct 30/15 WING MIDDLE SECTION BETWEEN SPAR I AND SPAR II - EXTERNAL   - INSPECTION/CHECK Revision Status: U - Unchanged, R - Revised, N - New, D - Deleted EMB-145  - AMM 1285 Chapter 05 TOC Page 15 of 32 Rev 55 - Oct 29/18 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="16" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL PAGEBLOCK REVISION REVISION TASK STATUS DATE 05-20-86-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 WING MIDDLE SECTION BETWEEN SPAR I AND SPAR II - EXTER-   NAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-87/600 U Oct 30/15 WING MIDDLE SECTION BETWEEN SPAR I AND SPAR II - INTERNAL -   INSPECTION/CHECK 05-20-87-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 WING MIDDLE SECTION BETWEEN SPAR I AND SPAR II - INTER-    NAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-88/600 U Oct 30/15 WING TIP SECTION BETWEEN SPAR I AND SPAR II - EXTERNAL - IN-    SPECTION/CHECK 05-20-88-200-802-A U Oct 30/15 WING TIP SECTION BETWEEN SPAR I AND SPAR II - EXTERNAL   GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-89/600 U Oct 30/15 WING TIP SECTION BETWEEN SPAR I AND SPAR II - INTERNAL - IN-   SPECTION/CHECK 05-20-89-200-801-A U Oct 31/17 WING TIP SECTION BETWEEN SPAR I AND SPAR II - INTERNAL   GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-90/600 U Oct 30/15 INBOARD FLAP - EXTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK   05-20-90-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 INBOARD FLAP GROUND SPOILER AND SPEED BRAKE - EXTER-   NAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-91/600 U Oct 30/15 INBOARD FLAP AND LOWER SHROUD / GROUD SPOILER / SPEED    BRAKE - INTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK 05-20-91-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 INBOARD FLAP AND LOWER SHROUD / GROUND SPOILER /    SPEED BRAKE 05-20-92/600 U Oct 30/15 OUTBOARD FLAP - EXTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK   Revision Status: U - Unchanged, R - Revised, N - New, D - Deleted EMB-145  - AMM 1285 Chapter 05 TOC Page 16 of 32 Rev 55 - Oct 29/18 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="17" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL PAGEBLOCK REVISION REVISION TASK STATUS DATE 05-20-92-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 OUTBOARD FLAP - EXTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION   05-20-93/600 U Oct 30/15 OUTBOARD FLAP - INTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK   05-20-93-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 OUTBOARD FLAP - INTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION    05-20-94/600 U Oct 30/15 AILERON - EXTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK    05-20-94-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 AILERON - EXTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION   05-20-95/600 U Oct 30/15 AILERON - INTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK   05-20-95-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 AILERON - INTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION   05-20-96/600 U Oct 30/15 CENTER WING LEADING EDGE - INTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK   05-20-96-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 CENTER WING LEADING EDGE - INTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL IN-   SPECTION 05-20-97/600 U Oct 30/15 CENTER FUSELAGE IV - PASSENGER CABIN TOP - INTERNAL - IN-    SPECTION/CHECK 05-20-97-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 CENTER FUSELAGE IV - PASSENGER CABIN TOP - INTERNAL    GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-20-98/600 U Oct 30/15 CENTER FUSELAGE IV - PASSENGER CABIN TOP - EXTERNAL - IN-   SPECTION/CHECK 05-20-98-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 CENTER FUSELAGE IV - PASSENGER CABIN TOP - EXTERNAL   GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION Revision Status: U - Unchanged, R - Revised, N - New, D - Deleted EMB-145  - AMM 1285 Chapter 05 TOC Page 17 of 32 Rev 55 - Oct 29/18 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="18" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL PAGEBLOCK REVISION REVISION TASK STATUS DATE 05-20-99/600 U Oct 30/15 CENTER FUSELAGE II - PASSENGER CABIN TOP - EXTERNAL - IN-   SPECTION/CHECK 05-20-99-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 CENTER FUSELAGE II - PASSENGER CABIN TOP - EXTERNAL GEN-   ERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-30-01/600 U Oct 30/15 NOSE LANDING GEAR - EXTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK    05-30-01-200-801-A R Oct 29/18 NOSE LANDING GEAR - EXTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION    05-30-03/600 U Oct 30/15 MAIN DOOR - EXTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK   05-30-03-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 MAIN DOOR - EXTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION   05-30-04/600 U Oct 30/15 MAIN DOOR - INSPECTION/CHECK   05-30-04-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 MAIN DOOR - INTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION   05-30-05/600 U Oct 30/15 ESCAPE HATCH - EXTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK   05-30-05-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 ESCAPE HATCH - EXTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION    05-30-06/600 U Oct 30/15 ESCAPE HATCH - INTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK    05-30-06-200-801-A U Apr 29/16 ESCAPE HATCH - INTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION   05-30-07/600 U Oct 30/15 BAGGAGE DOOR - EXTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK   05-30-07-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 BAGGAGE DOOR - EXTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION   Revision Status: U - Unchanged, R - Revised, N - New, D - Deleted EMB-145  - AMM 1285 Chapter 05 TOC Page 18 of 32 Rev 55 - Oct 29/18 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="19" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL PAGEBLOCK REVISION REVISION TASK STATUS DATE 05-30-08/600 U Oct 30/15 BAGGAGE DOOR - INTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK   05-30-08-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 BAGGAGE DOOR - INTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION   05-30-09/600 U Oct 30/15 SERVICE DOOR - EXTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK    05-30-09-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 SERVICE DOOR - EXTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION    05-30-10/600 U Oct 30/15 SERVICE DOOR - INTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK   05-30-10-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 SERVICE DOOR - INTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION   05-30-11/600 U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: EMB-145 LR/LU/MR/MP/MK/EU/EP/ER AND EMB-135   LR/KE/KL/ER WING-TO-FUSELAGE FAIRING - EXTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK 05-30-11-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: EMB-145 LR/LU/MR/MP/MK/EU/EP/ER and EMB-135   LR/KE/KL/ER WING-TO-FUSELAGE FAIRING - EXTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL IN- SPECTION 05-30-12/600 R Oct 29/18 WING-TO-FUSELAGE FAIRING - INTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK   05-30-12-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: EMB-145 LR/LU/MR/MP/MK and EMB-135 LR/KE/KL    WING-TO-FUSELAGE FAIRING - INTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL IN- SPECTION 05-30-13/600 U Oct 30/15 CENTER WING-TO-FUSELAGE FAIRING - EXTERNAL - INSPECTION/    CHECK 05-30-13-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 CENTER WING-TO-FUSELAGE FAIRING - EXTERNAL GENERAL VIS-   UAL INSPECTION Revision Status: U - Unchanged, R - Revised, N - New, D - Deleted EMB-145  - AMM 1285 Chapter 05 TOC Page 19 of 32 Rev 55 - Oct 29/18 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="20" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL PAGEBLOCK REVISION REVISION TASK STATUS DATE 05-30-14/600 U Oct 30/15 CENTER WING-TO-FUSELAGE FAIRING - INTERNAL - INSPECTION/   CHECK 05-30-14-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 CENTER WING-TO-FUSELAGE FAIRING - INTERNAL GENERAL VIS-   UAL INSPECTION 05-30-15/600 U Oct 30/15 REAR WING-TO-FUSELAGE FAIRING - EXTERNAL - INSPECTION/    CHECK 05-30-15-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 REAR WING-TO-FUSELAGE FAIRING - EXTERNAL GENERAL VISU-    AL INSPECTION 05-30-16/600 U Oct 30/15 REAR WING-TO-FUSELAGE FAIRING - INTERNAL - INSPECTION/   CHECK 05-30-16-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 REAR WING-TO-FUSELAGE FAIRING - INTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL   INSPECTION 05-30-17/600 U Oct 30/15 LATERAL WING-TO-FUSELAGE -FAIRING - EXTERNAL - INSPECTION/   CHECK 05-30-17-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 LATERAL WING-TO-FUSELAGE FAIRING - EXTERNAL GENERAL   VISUAL INSPECTION 05-30-18/600 U Oct 30/15 LATERAL WING-TO-FUSELAGE FAIRING - INTERNAL - INSPECTION/   CHECK 05-30-18-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 LATERAL WING-TO-FUSELAGE FAIRING - INTERNAL GENERAL VIS-    UAL INSPECTION 05-30-20/600 U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: EMB-145LR/LU/MR/MP/MK AND EMB-135LR/KE/KL MOD-    ELS CENTER FUSELAGE III - WING STUB LH/RH SIDES - EXTERNAL - IN- SPECTION/CHECK Revision Status: U - Unchanged, R - Revised, N - New, D - Deleted EMB-145  - AMM 1285 Chapter 05 TOC Page 20 of 32 Rev 55 - Oct 29/18 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="21" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL PAGEBLOCK REVISION REVISION TASK STATUS DATE 05-30-20-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: EMB-145LR/LU/MR/MP/MK AND EMB-135LR/KE/KL   MODELS CENTER FUSELAGE III - WING STUB LH/RH SIDES - EXTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-30-20-200-802-A U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: EMB-145LR/LU/MR/MP/MK AND EMB-135LR/KE/KL    MODELS CENTER FUSELAGE III - WING STUB LH/RH SIDES - EXTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-30-21/600 U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: EMB-145LR/LU/MR/MP/MK AND EMB-135LR/KE/KL MOD-    ELS CENTER FUSELAGE III - WING STUB LH/RH SIDES - INTERNAL - IN- SPECTION/CHECK 05-30-21-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: EMB-145LR/LU/MR/MP/MK AND EMB-135LR/KE/KL   MODELS CENTER FUSELAGE III - WING SUB LH/RH SIDES - INTERNAL GEN- ERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-30-22/600 CONFIG-1 U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: EMB-145LR/LU/MR/MP/MK AND EMB-135LR/KE/KL MOD-   ELS CENTER FUSELAGE III - WING STUB MIDDLE SECTION - EXTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK 05-30-22-200-801-A CONFIG-1 U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: EMB-145LR/LU/MR/MP/MK AND EMB-135LR/KE/KL   MODELS CENTER FUSELAGE III - WING STUB MIDDLE SECTION - EXTER- NAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-30-22/600 CONFIG-2 U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: EMB-145LR/LU/MR/MP/MK AND EMB-135LR/KE/KL MOD-   ELS CENTER FUSELAGE III - WING STUB MIDDLE SECTION - EXTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK 05-30-22-200-801-A CONFIG-2 U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: EMB-145LR/LU/MR/MP/MK AND EMB-135LR/KE/KL   MODELS CENTER FUSELAGE III - WING STUB MIDDLE SECTION - EXTER- NAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION Revision Status: U - Unchanged, R - Revised, N - New, D - Deleted EMB-145  - AMM 1285 Chapter 05 TOC Page 21 of 32 Rev 55 - Oct 29/18 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="22" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL PAGEBLOCK REVISION REVISION TASK STATUS DATE 05-30-23/600 U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: EMB-145LR/LU/MR/MP/MK AND EMB-135LR/KE/KL MOD-   ELS CENTER FUSELAGE III - WING STUB MIDDLE SECTION - INTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK 05-30-23-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: EMB-145LR/LU/MR/MP/MK AND EMB-135LR/KE/KL   MODELS CENTER FUSELAGE III - WING STUB MIDDLE SECTION - INTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-30-24/600 U Oct 30/15 MAIN LANDING GEAR - EXTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK    05-30-24-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 MAIN LANDING GEAR - EXTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION    05-30-25/600 U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: AIRCRAFT WITH SIDE-HINGED MAIN DOOR   SIDE-HINGED MAIN DOOR - INTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK 05-30-25-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: AIRCRAFT WITH SIDE-HINGED MAIN DOOR   SIDE-HINGED MAIN DOOR - INTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPEC- TION 05-30-27/600 U Oct 30/15 REAR FUSELAGE I - BAGGAGE COMPARTMENT TOP - EXTERNAL -   INSPECTION/CHECK 05-30-27-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 REAR FUSELAGE I - BAGGAGE COMPARTMENT TOP - EXTERNAL   GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-30-28/600 U Oct 30/15 GROUND SPOILER - EXTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK   05-30-28-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 GROUND SPOILER - EXTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION    05-30-29/600 U Oct 30/15 GROUND SPOILER - INTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK    05-30-29-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 GROUND SPOILER - INTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION   Revision Status: U - Unchanged, R - Revised, N - New, D - Deleted EMB-145  - AMM 1285 Chapter 05 TOC Page 22 of 32 Rev 55 - Oct 29/18 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="23" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL PAGEBLOCK REVISION REVISION TASK STATUS DATE 05-30-30/600 U Oct 30/15 SPEED BRAKE - EXTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK   05-30-30-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 SPEED BRAKE - EXTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION   05-30-31/600 U Oct 30/15 SPEED BRAKE - INTERNAL - INSPECTION/CHECK    05-30-31-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 SPEED BRAKE - INTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION    05-30-41/600 U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: FOR AIRCRAFT WITHOUT THRUST REVERSER ONLY   EXHAUST NOZZLE - INSPECTION/CHECK 05-30-41-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: FOR AIRCRAFT WITHOUT THRUST REVERSER ONLY   EXHAUST NOZZLE - EXTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-30-41-200-802-A U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: FOR AIRCRAFT WITHOUT THRUST REVERSER ONLY   EXHAUST NOZZLE - INTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-40-01/600 U Oct 30/15 EWIS COMPONENTS IN THE CENTER FUSELAGE III LOWER SIDE -   INSPECTION/CHECK 05-40-01-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 EWIS COMPONENTS IN THE CENTER FUSELAGE III (LOWER SIDE)   - INTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-40-01/700 U Oct 30/15 EWIS COMPONENTS IN THE CENTER FUSELAGE III LOWER SIDE -    CLEANING/PAINTING 05-40-01-100-801-A U Oct 30/15 EWIS COMPONENTS IN THE CENTER FUSELAGE III (LOWER SIDE)    - CLEANING 05-40-02/600 U Oct 30/15 EWIS COMPONENTS IN THE CENTER FUSELAGE IV LOWER SIDE -   INSPECTION/CHECK Revision Status: U - Unchanged, R - Revised, N - New, D - Deleted EMB-145  - AMM 1285 Chapter 05 TOC Page 23 of 32 Rev 55 - Oct 29/18 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="24" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL PAGEBLOCK REVISION REVISION TASK STATUS DATE 05-40-02-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 EWIS COMPONENTS IN THE CENTER FUSELAGE IV (LOWER SIDE)   - INTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-40-02/700 U Oct 30/15 EWIS COMPONENTS IN THE CENTER FUSELAGE IV LOWER SIDE -   CLEANING/PAINTING 05-40-02-100-801-A U Oct 30/15 EWIS COMPONENTS IN THE CENTER FUSELAGE IV (LOWER SIDE)    - CLEANING 05-40-03/700 U Oct 30/15 EWIS COMPONENTS IN THE CENTER FUSELAGE IV UPPER SIDE    SURROUDING ELT UNIT - CLEANING/PAINTING 05-40-03-100-801-A U Oct 30/15 EWIS COMPONENTS IN THE CENTER FUSELAGE IV (UPPER SIDE -   SURROUNDING ELT UNIT) - CLEANING 05-40-04/600 U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: ACFT WITH CLASS-D BAGGAGE COMPARTMENT   EWIS COMPONENTS IN THE REAR FUSELAGE I LOWER SIDE - IN- SPECTION/CHECK 05-40-04-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: ACFT WITH CLASS-D BAGGAGE COMPARTMENT   EWIS COMPONENTS IN THE REAR FUSELAGE I (LOWER SIDE) - IN- TERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-40-04/700 U Oct 30/15 EWIS COMPONENTS IN THE REAR FUSELAGE I LOWER SIDE -   CLEANING/PAINTING 05-40-04-100-801-A U Oct 30/15 EWIS COMPONENTS IN THE REAR FUSELAGE I (LOWER SIDE) -   CLEANING 05-40-05/600 U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: ACFT WITH CLASS-D BAGGAGE COMPARTMENT    EWIS COMPONENTS IN THE REAR FUSELAGE I LATERAL SIDE - IN- SPECTION/CHECK 05-40-05-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: ACFT WITH CLASS-D BAGGAGE COMPARTMENT    EWIS COMPONENTS IN THE REAR FUSELAGE I (LATERAL SIDE) - INTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION Revision Status: U - Unchanged, R - Revised, N - New, D - Deleted EMB-145  - AMM 1285 Chapter 05 TOC Page 24 of 32 Rev 55 - Oct 29/18 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="25" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL PAGEBLOCK REVISION REVISION TASK STATUS DATE 05-40-05/700 U Oct 30/15 EWIS COMPONENTS IN THE REAR FUSELAGE I LATERAL SIDE -   CLEANING/PAINTING 05-40-05-100-801-A U Oct 30/15 EWIS COMPONENTS IN THE REAR FUSELAGE I (LATERAL SIDE) -   CLEANING 05-40-06/600 U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: ACFT WITH CLASS-D BAGGAGE COMPARTMENT    EWIS COMPONENTS IN THE REAR FUSELAGE I UPPER SIDE - IN- SPECTION/CHECK 05-40-06-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: ACFT WITH CLASS-D BAGGAGE COMPARTMENT    EWIS COMPONENTS IN THE REAR FUSELAGE I (UPPER SIDE) - IN- TERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-40-07/600 U Oct 30/15 EWIS COMPONENTS IN THE REAR FUSELAGE I PRESSURE BULK-   HEAD PRESSURIZED AREA - INSPECTION/CHECK 05-40-07-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 EWIS COMPONENTS IN THE REAR FUSELAGE I (PRESSURE BULK-   HEAD PRESSURIZED AREA) - INTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL IN- SPECTION 05-40-08/600 U Oct 30/15 EWIS COMPONENTS IN THE REAR FUSELAGE II AFT AREA OF REAR   PRESSURE BULKHEAD - INSPECTION/CHECK 05-40-08-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 EWIS COMPONENTS IN THE REAR FUSELAGE II (AFT AREA OF   REAR PRESSURE BULKHEAD) - INTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL IN- SPECTION 05-40-09/600 U Oct 30/15 EWIS COMPONENTS IN THE WING-TO-FUSELAGE FAIRING AREA -   INSPECTION/CHECK 05-40-09-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 EWIS COMPONENTS IN THE WING-TO-FUSELAGE FAIRING AREA -    INTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION Revision Status: U - Unchanged, R - Revised, N - New, D - Deleted EMB-145  - AMM 1285 Chapter 05 TOC Page 25 of 32 Rev 55 - Oct 29/18 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="26" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL PAGEBLOCK REVISION REVISION TASK STATUS DATE 05-40-10/600 U Oct 30/15 EWIS COMPONENTS IN THE CENTER FUSELAGE II (LOWER SIDE) -   INSPECTION/CHECK 05-40-10-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 EWIS COMPONENTS IN THE CENTER FUSELAGE II (LOWER SIDE) -   DETAILED VISUAL INSPECTION 05-40-10/700 U Oct 30/15 EWIS COMPONENTS IN THE CENTER FUSELAGE II (LOWER SIDE) -    CLEANING/PAINTING 05-40-10-100-801-A U Oct 30/15 EWIS COMPONENTS IN THE CENTER FUSELAGE II (LOWER SIDE) -    CLEANING 05-40-11/600 U Oct 30/15 EWIS COMPONENTS IN THE FORWARD FUSELAGE I (NLG AND   ELECTRONIC COMPARTMENTS AND PRESSURE BULKHEAD-UPPER SIDE) - INSPECTION/CHECK 05-40-11-200-801-A U Apr 29/16 EWIS COMPONENTS IN FORWARD FUSELAGE I (NLG ELECTRONIC   COMPARTMENT)- GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION 05-40-11-200-802-A U Oct 30/15 EWIS COMPONENTS IN THE FORWARD FUSELAGE I (FWD ELEC-   TRONIC COMPARTMENT AND FWD PRESSURE BULKHEAD - UP- PER SIDE) - DETAILED VISUAL INSPECTION 05-40-11/700 U Oct 30/15 EWIS COMPONENTS IN THE FORWARD FUSELAGE I (NLG AND   ELECTRONIC COMPARTMENTS AND PRESSURE BULKHEAD-UPPER SIDE) - CLEANING/PAINTING 05-40-11-100-801-A U Oct 30/15 EWIS COMPONENTS IN THE FORWARD FUSELAGE I (NLG &amp; FWD   ELECTRONIC COMPARTMENTS FWD PRESSURE BULKHEAD - UP- PER SIDE) - CLEANING 05-40-12/600 U Oct 30/15 EWIS COMPONENTS IN THE FORWARD FUSELAGE II (LOWER SIDE)    - INSPECTION/CHECK 05-40-12-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 EWIS COMPONENTS IN THE FORWARD FUSELAGE II (COCKPIT    LOWER SIDE)- DETAILED INSPECTION Revision Status: U - Unchanged, R - Revised, N - New, D - Deleted EMB-145  - AMM 1285 Chapter 05 TOC Page 26 of 32 Rev 55 - Oct 29/18 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="27" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL PAGEBLOCK REVISION REVISION TASK STATUS DATE 05-40-12/700 U Oct 30/15 EWIS COMPONENTS IN THE FORWARD FUSELAGE II (LOWER SIDE)   - CLEANING/PAINTING 05-40-12-100-801-A U Oct 30/15 EWIS COMPONENTS IN THE FORWARD FUSELAGE II (COCKPIT   LOWER SIDE)- CLEANING 05-40-13/600 U Oct 30/15 EWIS COMPONENTS IN THE FOWARD FUSELAGE II (LATERAL SIDE)    - INSPECTION/CHECK 05-40-13-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 EWIS COMPONENTS IN THE FORWARD FUSELAGE II (COCKPIT    LATERAL SIDE) - DETAILED INSPECTION 05-40-13/700 U Oct 30/15 EWIS COMPONENTS IN THE FOWARD FUSELAGE II (LATERAL SIDE)   - CLEANING/PAINTING 05-40-13-100-801-A R Oct 29/18 EWIS COMPONENTS IN FORWARD FUSELAGE II - CLEANING   05-40-14/600 U Oct 30/15 EWIS COMPONENTS IN THE CENTER FUSELAGE I (LOWER SIDE) -   INSPECTION/CHECK 05-40-14-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 EWIS COMPONENTS IN THE CENTER FUSELAGE I (LOWER SIDE) -   DETAILED VISUAL INSPECTION 05-40-14/700 U Oct 30/15 EWIS COMPONENTS IN THE CENTER FUSELAGE I (LOWER SIDE) -   CLEANING/PAINTING 05-40-14-100-801-A U Oct 30/15 EWIS COMPONENTS IN THE CENTER FUSELAGE I (LOWER SIDE) -    CLEANING 05-40-15/600 U Oct 30/15 EWIS COMPONENTS IN THE ENGINE PYLON - INSPECTION/CHECK    05-40-15-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 EWIS COMPONENTS IN THE PYLON - INTERNAL GENERAL VISUAL   INSPECTION Revision Status: U - Unchanged, R - Revised, N - New, D - Deleted EMB-145  - AMM 1285 Chapter 05 TOC Page 27 of 32 Rev 55 - Oct 29/18 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="28" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL PAGEBLOCK REVISION REVISION TASK STATUS DATE 05-40-16/600 U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: FOR ACFT EMB-145LR/LU/MR/MP/MK/XR AND   EMB-135LR/KE/KL MODELS EWIS COMPONENTS IN THE CENTER FUSELAGE III (WING STUB AREA) - INSPECTION/CHECK 05-40-16-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: FOR ACFT EMB-145LR/LU/MR/MP/MK/XR AND   EMB-135LR/KE/KL MODELS EWIS COMPONENTS IN THE CENTER FUSELAGE III (WING TANK UNIT HARNESS) - DETAILED VISUAL INSPECTION 05-40-18/600 U Oct 30/15 EWIS COMPONENTS IN THE ENGINE - INSPECTION/CHECK    05-40-18-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 EWIS COMPONENTS IN THE ENGINE - INTERNAL GENERAL VISU-    AL INSPECTION 05-50-01/600 U Oct 30/15 LIGHTNING STRIKE - INSPECTION/CHECK   05-50-01-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 LIGHTNING STRIKE - GENERAL INSPECTION   05-50-01-200-802-A U Oct 30/15 FORWARD FUSELAGE AND NOSE LANDING GEAR - DETAILED IN-   SPECTION 05-50-01-200-803-A U Oct 30/15 CENTER FUSELAGE MAIN LANDING GEARS AND WING STUB - IN-   SPECTION 05-50-01-200-804-A U Oct 30/15 WINGS - DETAILED INSPECTION    05-50-01-200-805-A U Oct 30/15 ENGINE NACELLE - DETAILED INSPECTION    05-50-01-200-806-A U Oct 30/15 REAR FUSELAGE AND EMPENNAGE - DETAILED INSPECTION   05-50-02/600 U Oct 30/15 HARD LANDING - INSPECTION/CHECK   05-50-02-200-801-A U Apr 27/18 HARD LANDING   Revision Status: U - Unchanged, R - Revised, N - New, D - Deleted EMB-145  - AMM 1285 Chapter 05 TOC Page 28 of 32 Rev 55 - Oct 29/18 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="29" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL PAGEBLOCK REVISION REVISION TASK STATUS DATE 05-50-03/600 U Oct 30/15 HIGH DRAG/SIDE LOAD LANDING CONDITION - INSPECTION/CHECK   05-50-03-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 HIGH DRAG/SIDE LOAD LANDING CONDITION   05-50-04/600 U Oct 30/15 MAXIMUM OPERATING SPEED ENVELOPE EXCEEDED - INSPEC-    TION/CHECK 05-50-04-200-801-A U Apr 27/18 OVERSPEED INSPECTION    05-50-05/600 U Oct 30/15 HIGH LOAD FACTOR FLIGHT - INSPECTION/CHECK   05-50-05-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 HIGH-LOAD-FACTOR FLIGHT CONDITION   05-50-06/600 U Oct 30/15 LANDING GEAR DOWN OVERSPEED - INSPECTION/CHECK   05-50-06-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 LANDING GEAR DOWN OVERSPEED   05-50-07/600 U Oct 30/15 MAXIMUM FLAP EXTENDED SPEED - INSPECTION/CHECK   05-50-07-200-801-A R Oct 29/18 MAXIMUM FLAP EXTENDED SPEED    05-50-08/600 U Oct 30/15 BIRD STRIKE AND HAILSTORM - INSPECTION/CHECK    05-50-08-200-802-A U Feb 16/16 BIRD STRIKE   05-50-08-200-803-A U Oct 30/15 HAILSTORM   05-50-09/600 U Oct 30/15 ENGINE FIRE WARNING - INSPECTION/CHECK   05-50-09-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 ENGINE FIRE WARNING   Revision Status: U - Unchanged, R - Revised, N - New, D - Deleted EMB-145  - AMM 1285 Chapter 05 TOC Page 29 of 32 Rev 55 - Oct 29/18 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="30" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL PAGEBLOCK REVISION REVISION TASK STATUS DATE 05-50-10/600 U Oct 30/15 ICE OR SNOW CONDITION - INSPECTION/CHECK   05-50-10-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 ICING OR SNOWING INSPECTION   05-50-11/600 U Oct 30/15 APU FIRE WARNING - INSPECTION/CHECK    05-50-11-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 APU FIRE WARNING    05-50-12/600 U Oct 30/15 TOILET OVERSERVICING - INSPECTION/CHECK   05-50-12-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 TOILET OVERSERVICING - INSPECTION   05-50-12/700 CONFIG-1 U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: ACFT MODEL(S) EMB-145   TOILET OVERSERVICING - CLEANING/PAINTING 05-50-12-100-801-A CONFIG-1 U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: ACFT MODEL(S) EMB-145   TOILET OVERSERVICING - CLEANING 05-50-12/700 CONFIG-2 U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: ACFT MODEL(S) EMB-135   TOILET OVERSERVICING - CLEANING/PAINTING 05-50-12-100-801-A CONFIG-2 U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: ACFT MODEL(S) EMB-135    TOILET OVERSERVICING - CLEANING 05-50-13/600 U Oct 30/15 LANDING GEAR FREE-FALL CONDITION - INSPECTION/CHECK    05-50-13-700-801-A U Oct 30/15 AIRCRAFT RECONFIGURATION - CHECK   05-50-14/600 U Oct 30/15 OVERHEATED WHEELS - INSPECTION/CHECK   05-50-14-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 OVERHEAT WHEELS   Revision Status: U - Unchanged, R - Revised, N - New, D - Deleted EMB-145  - AMM 1285 Chapter 05 TOC Page 30 of 32 Rev 55 - Oct 29/18 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="31" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL PAGEBLOCK REVISION REVISION TASK STATUS DATE 05-50-15/600 U Oct 30/15 LANDING GEAR TIRE TREAD FAILURE - INSPECTION/CHECK   05-50-15-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 LANDING-GEAR TIRE TREAD FAILURE - EXTENDED LANDING   GEAR 05-50-15-200-802-A U Oct 30/15 LANDING-GEAR TIRE TREAD FAILURE - RETRACTED LANDING    GEAR 05-50-16/600 U Oct 30/15 HIGH ENERGY STOP - INSPECTION/CHECK    05-50-16-200-801-A U Feb 16/16 HIGH ENERGY STOP - INSPECTION   05-50-18/600 U Feb 16/16 VOLCANIC ASH - INSPECTION/CHECK   05-50-18-200-801-A U Oct 31/16 VOLCANIC ASH CONDITION   05-50-19/600 U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: AIRCRAFT WITH APU T-62T-40C14   FUEL PUMP FAILURE - INSPECTION/CHECK 05-50-19-960-801-A U Oct 30/15 EFFECTIVITY: AIRCRAFT WITH APU T-62T-40C14   APU FUEL INLET FILTER - INSPECTION 05-50-23/600 U Oct 30/15 BRAKE USE DURING TOWBARLESS TOWING OPERATION - INSPEC-    TION/CHECK 05-50-23-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 BRAKE USE DURING TOWBARLESS TOWING OPERATION    05-50-24/600 U Oct 30/15 LH/RH STATIC PORTS VICINITY - INSPECTION/CHECK   05-50-24-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 LH/RH STATIC PORTS VICINITY - INSPECTION   05-50-25/600 U Oct 30/15 OVERWEIGHT LANDING - INSPECTION/CHECK   Revision Status: U - Unchanged, R - Revised, N - New, D - Deleted EMB-145  - AMM 1285 Chapter 05 TOC Page 31 of 32 Rev 55 - Oct 29/18 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="32" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL PAGEBLOCK REVISION REVISION TASK STATUS DATE 05-50-25-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 OVERWEIGHT LANDING   05-50-26/600 U Oct 30/15 ON-GROUND GALE-FORCE WINDS - INSPECTION/CHECK   05-50-26-200-802-A R Oct 29/18 ON-GROUND GALE-FORCE WINDS    05-50-27/600 U Oct 30/15 SEVERE TURBULENCE OR MANEUVERS BUFFETING CONDITION -    INSPECTION/CHECK 05-50-27-200-801-A U Oct 31/16 SEVERE TURBULENCE OR MANEUVERS OR BUFFETING CONDI-   TION 05-50-28/600 U Feb 16/16 OPERATION IN SANDSTORM CONDITIONS - INSPECTION/CHECK   05-50-28-200-801-A R Oct 29/18 OPERATION IN SANDSTORM CONDITIONS   05-50-32/600 U Oct 30/15 OVERSTEERING - INSPECTION/CHECK   05-50-32-200-801-A U Oct 31/16 OVERSTEERING - GENERAL VISUAL INSPECTION   05-50-34/600 U Oct 30/15 FLAP ALTITUDE EXCEEDANCE - INSPECTION/CHECK    05-50-34-200-801-A U Oct 30/15 FLAP ALTITUDE EXCEEDANCE - INSPECTION/CHECK    05-51-01/600 U Oct 30/15 HIRF/LIGHTNING - INSPECTION/CHECK   05-51-01-200-801-A U Feb 16/16 HIRF/LIGHTNING PROTECTION - INSPECTION   Revision Status: U - Unchanged, R - Revised, N - New, D - Deleted EMB-145  - AMM 1285 Chapter 05 TOC Page 32 of 32 Rev 55 - Oct 29/18 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
	</pages>
</metadata>
