<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<metadata id="MPP1285_34-31-00-05-1">
  <file family="145" manual="AMM" pn="1285" chg="U" tsn="51" is_tr="false">
    <title>AMM PART II-1285 - CHAPTER 34-31-00-05 - RADIO ALTIMETER - ADJUSTMENT/TEST</title>
    <path>/CHAPTER_34</path>
    <hash>5ae833e901c1ac476f75fe8c7a66fff0</hash>
  </file>
  <pages>
    <page number="1" width="216.0" height="279.0">
      <data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL RADIO ALTIMETER - ADJUSTMENT/TEST EFFECTIVITY:  ALL 1. General A. This section gives the procedures to do the operational test of the radio altimeter system and its adjustment. B. The procedures in this section are given in the sequence below. The tasks identified with ( &#x2666;) are part of the Scheduled Maintenance Requirements Document (SMRD). TASK NUMBER DESCRIPTION EFFECTIVITY RADIO ALTIMETER SYSTEM - OPERA- ALL 34-31-00-700-801-A TIONAL TEST  ALL 34-31-00-820-801-A RADIO ALTIMETER - ADJUSTMENT   EMB-145  - AMM 1285 General 34-31-00 Page 1 of 11 Rev 48 - Oct  30/15 Copyright © by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
    </page>
    <page number="2" width="216.0" height="279.0">
      <data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL TASK 34-31-00-700-801-A EFFECTIVITY:  ALL 2. RADIO ALTIMETER SYSTEM - OPERATIONAL TEST A. General (1) This task gives the procedures to do the operational test of the radio altimeter system. To do this test it is necessary to simulate a flight condition. B. References REFERENCE DESIGNATION AMM SDS 34-22-00/1  AMM SDS 34-31-00/1  ENERGIZATION OF THE AIRCRAFT WITH AN EX- AMM TASK 20-40-01-860-801-A/200 TERNAL POWER SOURCE AMM TASK 34-31-00-820-801-A/500 RADIO ALTIMETER - ADJUSTMENT C. Zones and Accesses Not Applicable D. Tools and Equipment Not Applicable E. Auxiliary Items Not Applicable F. Consumable Materials Not Applicable G. Expandable Parts Not Applicable H. Persons Recommended QTY FUNCTION PLACE 1 Does the task Cockpit I. Preparation SUBTASK 841-002-A (1) Energize the aircraft with the external DC power supply ( AMM TASK 20-40-01-860-801-A/200). (2) On the electrical control panel, set the BATT 1 and BATT 2 rotary switches to OFF position. (3) Put the aircraft in the flight configuration (AIR) as follows: (a) Aircraft on the ground. (b) On the circuit breaker panel, open the AIR/GND A, B, C, and D circuit breakers. EMB-145  - AMM 1285 700-801-A/500 34-31-00 Page 2 of 11 Rev 48 - Oct  30/15 Copyright © by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
    </page>
    <page number="3" width="216.0" height="279.0">
      <data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL Result: 1 Make sure that the AIR/GND FAIL caution message is shown on the EICAS. (4) Make sure that the systems below are operational and on: &#x2013; Radio Altimeter System (AMM SDS 34-31-00/1). &#x2013; EFIS (AMM SDS 34-22-00/1). J. Test Procedures (Figure 501)  (Figure 502)  SUBTASK 710-002-A (1) Do the check of the radio altimeter 1 as follows: (a) On the PFD 1, make sure that the radio altimeter indication is 0 ± 5 feet. If the radio altimeter indication is out of 0 ± 5 feet, adjust the radio altimeter ( AMM TASK 34-31-00-820-801-A/500). NOTE: If the radio altimeter is defective or if the indication is not valid, the radio altimeter digits are replaced by (amber) RA with dash on the PFD. (b) Push and hold the RA/TEST button on the DC-550 1. Result: 1 On the PFD 1, the radio altitude field indicates 100 ± 10 feet. 2 (For aircraft with one radio altimeter connected to egpws) On the EICAS display, the GPWS INOP and WINDSHEAR INOP caution messages come into view. (For aircraft with two radio altimeters connected to egpws) These messages do not come into view on the EICAS. 3 On the PFD 1, the TEST (pink) message is shown. (This TEST message appears because the IC-600 starts the test mode, too). (c) Release the radio altimeter test button on the DC-550 1. (2) (For aircraft equipped with radio altimeter 2) Do the check of radio altimeter 2 as follows: (a) On the PFD 2, make sure that the radio altimeter indication is 0 ± 5 feet. If the radio altimeter indication is out of 0 ± 5 feet, adjust the radio altimeter ( AMM TASK 34-31-00-820-801-A/500). NOTE: If the radio altimeter is defective or if the indication is not valid, the radio altimeter digits are replaced by (amber) RA with dash on the PFD. (b) Push and hold the RA/TEST button on the DC-550 2. Result: 1 On the PFD 2, the radio altitude field indicates 100 ± 10 feet. 2 On the PFD 2, the TEST (pink) message is shown. (This TEST message appears because the IC-600 starts the test mode, too). (c) Release the radio altimeter test button on the DC-550 2. EMB-145  - AMM 1285 700-801-A/500 34-31-00 Page 3 of 11 Rev 48 - Oct  30/15 Copyright © by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
    </page>
    <page number="4" width="216.0" height="279.0">
      <data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL K. Follow-on SUBTASK 842-002-A (1) To put the aircraft in the ground configuration again, do as follows: (a) On the circuit breaker panel, close the AIR/GND A, B, C, and D circuit breakers for 10 seconds maximum. Result: 1 Make sure that the AIR/GND FAIL caution message is not shown on the EICAS. (2) Deenergize the aircraft ( AMM TASK 20-40-01-860-801-A/200). EMB-145  - AMM 1285 700-801-A/500 34-31-00 Page 4 of 11 Rev 48 - Oct  30/15 Copyright © by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
    </page>
    <page number="5" width="216.0" height="279.0">
      <data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL EFFECTIVITY: ALL DC-550 - Radio Altimeter - Test Controller  Figure 501 A FULL GSPD ET NAV FMS TTG WX OFF NAV 1 ADF FMS RA TEST DET. A 145AMM340021.MCE A EMB-145  - AMM 1285 700-801-A/500 34-31-00 Page 5 of 11 Rev 48 - Oct  30/15 Copyright © by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details. FMS ADF NAV 2 OFF BRG BRG</data>
    </page>
    <page number="6" width="216.0" height="279.0">
      <data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL EFFECTIVITY: ALL PFDs Indic