<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata id="MPP1285_06-10-00-01-1">
	<file family="145" manual="AMM" pn="1285" chg="U" tsn="51" is_tr="false">
		<title>AMM PART II-1285 - CHAPTER 06-10-00-01 - CONFIG-1 - MAIN DIMENSIONS AND AREAS - COMPONENT LOCATION</title>
		<path>/CHAPTER_06</path>
		<hash>2a5c6c6aa9c918473b480c56f2ce9a02</hash>
	</file>
	<pages>
		<page number="1" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL MAIN DIMENSIONS AND AREAS - COMPONENT LOCATION EFFECTIVITY:  ACFT MODEL(S) EMB-145 1. General A. This section gives the principal dimensions (Figure 101) for the wing surfaces, horizontal stabilizer surfaces, vertical stabilizer surfaces, and fuselage. EMB-145  - AMM 1285 General CONFIG-1 06-10-00 Page 1 of 5 Rev 48 - Oct  30/15 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="2" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL MAIN DIMENSIONS AND AREAS - COMPONENT LOCATION EFFECTIVITY:  ACFT MODEL(S) EMB-145 2. Dimensions A. Total Aircraft Table 101 Length 29.87 m (98 ft 0 in) Width 20.04 m (65 ft 9 in) Height 6.76 m (22 ft 2 in) B. Wing Table 102 Span 20.04 m (65.75 ft) 2 2 Area (reference wing) 51.18 m (550.89 ft ) Chord at root (reference wing) 4.086 m (13.41 ft) Chord at tip (reference wing) 1.038 m (3.41 ft) Dihedral at wing reference plane 3.5Â° Sweepback at 25% (reference wing) 22.73Â° C. Aileron Table 103 Span (WRP projection, measured on hinge 2.42 m (7.94 ft) line) Chord at root (normal to hinge line) 0.422 m (1.38 ft) Chord at tip (streamwise) 0.280 m (0.92 ft) D. Flaps Table 104  INBOARD FLAP OUTBOARD FLAP Span 2.59 m (8.50 ft) 3.34 m (10.96 ft) 2 2.25 m 2 2 Area 1.93 m (20.77 ft ) 2 (24.22 ft ) Chord at root 0.870 m (2.85 ft) 0.865 m (2.84 ft) Chord at tip 0.618 m (2.03 ft) 0.484 m (1.59 ft) E. Speed breaker/ground spoiler Table 105 Span 1.371 m (4.49 ft) 2 2 Area 0.560 m (6.03 ft ) F. Ground spoiler EMB-145  - AMM 1285 PGBLK 100 CONFIG-1 06-10-00 Page 2 of 5 Rev 48 - Oct  30/15 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="3" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL Table 106 Span 1.316 m (4.32 ft) 2 2 Area 0.600 m (6.46 ft ) G. Horizontal Tail Table 107 2 2 Area 11.20 m (120.53 ft ) Span 7.404 m (24.29 ft) Chord at root 1.894 m (6.21 ft) Chord at tip 1.11 m (3.64 ft) Dihedral 0Â° Sweepback at 25% chord line 17.79Â° H. Elevator Table 108 Hinge line 70% chord 2 2 Area aft of hinge line (two sides) 3.34 m (35.95 ft ) I. Vertical Tail Table 109 Span 2.78 m (9.12 ft) Chord at root 3.18 m (10.43 ft) Chord at tip 2.00 m (6.56 ft) Sweepback at 25% chordline 34.33Â° Position of rudder I hinge line 70% chord Position of rudder II hinge line 85% chord 2 2 Rudder area aft of rudder I hinge line 2.071 m (22.29 ft ) 2 2 Dorsal fin area 1.43 m (15.39 ft ) J. Pylon Table 110 2 2 Area 1.94 m (20.88 ft ) Chord at root (reference pylon) 3.611 m (11.85 ft) Chord at tip (reference pylon) 3.456 m (11.34 ft) Dihedral at pylon reference plane 4Â° K. Nacelle Table 111 Length 4.329 m (14.20 ft) Maximum width 1.307 m (4.29 ft) EMB-145  - AMM 1285 PGBLK 100 CONFIG-1 06-10-00 Page 3 of 5 Rev 48 - Oct  30/15 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="4" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL Table 111 (Continued) Maximum height 1.539 m (5.05 ft) L. Fuselage Table 112 Total length 27.929 m (91.63 ft) Length of pressurized section 23.222 m (76.19 ft) Outside diameter 2.280 m (7.48 ft) M. Aircraft Wetted Surface Area Table 113 2 2 SURFACE AREA m (ft ) Fuselage 165.5 (1781.4) Wing 84.6 (910.6) Horizontal Stabilizer 22.4 (241.1) Vertical Stabilizer 14.4 (155.0) Nacelles 32.5 (349.8) Pylon 7.8 (84.0) TOTAL 327.2 (3521.9) EMB-145  - AMM 1285 PGBLK 100 CONFIG-1 06-10-00 Page 4 of 5 Rev 48 - Oct  30/15 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="5" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL EFFECTIVITY: ALL Principal Dimensions  Figure 101 6.75 m 22 ft 2 in 2.20 m 14.44 m 7 ft   3 in 47 ft   5 in 27.93 m 91 ft  8 in 29.87 m 98 ft  0 in 7.55 m 24 ft  9 in 4.10 m 13 ft 5 in 20.04 m 65 ft  9 in EM145AMM060011A.DGN EMB-145  - AMM 1285 PGBLK 100 CONFIG-1 06-10-00 Page 5 of 5 Rev 48 - Oct  30/15 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="6" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data/>
		</page>
	</pages>
</metadata>
