<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata id="MPP1285_06-42-00-01-1">
	<file family="145" manual="AMM" pn="1285" chg="R" tsn="53" is_tr="false">
		<title>AMM PART II-1285 - CHAPTER 06-42-00-01 - TAIL CONE AND EMPENNAGE GROUP (MAJOR ZONE 300) ACCESS DOORS AND PANELS - COMPONENT LOCATION</title>
		<path>/CHAPTER_06</path>
		<hash>dc661d9795fb16f50f6c73a768b8a7a2</hash>
	</file>
	<pages>
		<page number="1" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL TAIL CONE AND EMPENNAGE GROUP (MAJOR ZONE 300) ACCESS DOORS AND PANELS - COMPONENT LOCATION EFFECTIVITY: ACFT MODEL(S) EMB-145 1. General A. This section gives the location of the access doors and panels in major zone 300 (tail cone and empennage group). EMB-145  - AMM 1285 General CONFIG-1 06-42-00 Page 1 of 11 Rev 53 - Oct 31/17 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="2" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL TAIL CONE AND EMPENNAGE GROUP (MAJOR ZONE 300) ACCESS DOORS AND PANELS - COMPONENT LOCATION EFFECTIVITY: ACFT MODEL(S) EMB-145 2. List of the Equipment and Components A. Table 101 (Sub-zone 310), Table 102 (Sub-zone 320), and Table 103 (Sub-zone 330) give the equipment and components to which you can get access through the access doors and panels. Table 101 - SUB-ZONE 310 DOOR OR PANEL TYPE OF IDENTIFICATION NUMBER EQUIPMENT/COMPONENTS ACCESS LEFT RIGHT Control cables, Fire extinguishing bottles of engine/ APU, Thrust reverser isolator control unit, APU fuel  312AR (Figure 102) Door pressure switch, check valve for aircraft with Class C baggage compartment 313AL (Figure 102) Access panel Attachment of tail cone (APU cowling) 313BL (Figure 102) Access panel Attachment of tail cone (APU cowling) APU support structure, Fuel line and filter, APU chip 313CL (Figure 102) Access door detector, APU exciter box, APU fuel shutoff solenoid valve, Oil dipstick and replenishment, APU drain line  313DR (Figure 102) Access panel Attachment of tail cone (APU cowling) [1]  Access panel APU air intake 313ER (Figure 101) APU air intake, Attachment of tail cone (APU cowl- [2]  313ER (Figure 102) Access panel ing), Air inlet silencer, Air inlet duct, Anti surge valve, APU fuel control assembly, Flow divider [1]  313FR (Figure 101) Fairing APU starter generator air output [1]  313GR (Figure 101) Access panel Attachment of tail cone (APU cowling) [1] Valid for aircraft without APU cowling 145-54858 series [2] Valid for aircraft with APU cowling 145-54858 series Table 102 - SUB-ZONE 320 DOOR OR PANEL TYPE OF IDENTIFICATION NUMBER EQUIPMENT/COMPONENTS ACCESS LEFT RIGHT 321AL (Figure 105) Fairing Control cables 321BL (Figure 105) Fairing Control cables 321CL (Figure 105) Fairing Control cables  321DR (Figure 105) Fairing Control cables Control cables and differential pressure switch of the 321EL (Figure 105) Fairing horizontal stabilizer anti-icing system 321FL (Figure 105) Fairing Control cables 322AL (Figure 103) Access panel Horizontal stabilizer anti-ice shutoff valve Horizontal stabilizer low pressure switch, Horizontal  322BR (Figure 104) Access panel stabilizer overpressure switch, VOR/LOC coupler 324AL (Figure 103) Access panel Control cables 324BL (Figure 103) Access panel Control cables 324CL (Figure 103) Access panel Control cables 324DL (Figure 103) Access panel Control cables Horizontal stabilizer actuator, electrical connectors, 324EL (Figure 103) 324FR (Figure 104) Access panel electrical wiring, Horizontal stab low pressure switches, Horizontal stab overpressure switch EMB-145  - AMM 1285 PGBLK 100 CONFIG-1 06-42-00 Page 2 of 11 Rev 53 - Oct 31/17 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="3" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL Table 102 - SUB-ZONE 320 (Continued) DOOR OR PANEL TYPE OF IDENTIFICATION NUMBER EQUIPMENT/COMPONENTS ACCESS LEFT RIGHT Rudder control hydraulic unit, Rudder control rod, Hy- 325AL (Figure 103) Access panel draulic tubing 325BL (Figure 103) Access panel Bellcrank, control cables 325CL (Figure 103) Access panel Rudder hydraulic actuators, feedback rod 325DL (Figure 103) Access panel Rudder actuator hinge, feedback rod hinge Bellcrank, control cables, duct leak sensor, anti-ice 325EL (Figure 103) Access panel duct junction 325FL (Figure 103) Access panel Elevator control cable  325FR (Figure 104) Access panel Control cables, Hydraulic tubing  325GR (Figure 104) Access panel Rudder control hydraulic unit Hydraulic lines, feedback rod, control cables, electri-  325HR (Figure 104) Access panel cal harness  325JR (Figure 104) Access panel Rudder actuator bellcrank, control cables  325KR (Figure 104) Access panel Control cables, bellcrank and electrical harness Elevator control bellcrank, duct leak sensor, anti-ice  325LR (Figure 104) Access panel duct 326AL (Figure 103) Access panel Rudder I lower hinge 326BL (Figure 103) Access panel Rudder I center hinge 326CL (Figure 103) Access panel Rudder II actuating rod 326DL (Figure 103) Access panel Rudder actuator hinges, feedback rod hinge 326EL (Figure 103) Access panel Rudder I center hinge 326FL (Figure 103) Access panel Rudder II actuating rod 326GL (Figure 103) Access panel Rudder I upper hinge 326HL (Figure 103) Access panel Rudder I upper hinge 327AL (Figure 103) Access panel Rudder II structure 327BL (Figure 103) Access panel Rudder II structure 327CL (Figure 103) Access panel Rudder II structure 327DL (Figure 103) Access panel Rudder II structure  327ER (Figure 104) Access panel Rudder II lower hinge  327FR (Figure 104) Access panel Rudder II center hinge, Rudder II actuating rod hinge  327GR (Figure 104) Access panel Rudder II center hinge, Rudder II actuating rod hinge  327HR (Figure 104) Access panel Rudder II upper hinge Table 103 - SUB-ZONE 330 DOOR OR PANEL TYPE OF IDENTIFICATION NUMBER EQUIPMENT/COMPONENTS ACCESS LEFT RIGHT 333AB (Figure 106) 334AB (Figure 107) Access panel Stabilizer structure 333BB (Figure 106) 334BB (Figure 107) Access panel Logolight 333CB (Figure 106) 334CB (Figure 107) Access panel Stabilizer structure Test point of the differential pressure switch of the 333DL (Figure 106) 334DR (Figure 107) Access panel horizontal stabilizer thermal anti-icing system 335AB (Figure 106) 336AB (Figure 107) Access panel Spring tab actuator 335BB (Figure 106) 336BB (Figure 107) Access panel Elevator hinge 335CB (Figure 106) 336CB (Figure 107) Access panel Elevator hinge EMB-145  - AMM 1285 PGBLK 100 CONFIG-1 06-42-00 Page 3 of 11 Rev 53 - Oct 31/17 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="4" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL Table 103 - SUB-ZONE 330 (Continued) DOOR OR PANEL TYPE OF IDENTIFICATION NUMBER EQUIPMENT/COMPONENTS ACCESS LEFT RIGHT 335DB (Figure 106) 336DB (Figure 107) Access panel Trim tab and elevator hinge [1] 335EB (Figure 106) 336EB (Figure 107) Access panel Tim tab hinge, FDR elevator RVDT/RVIT  335FB (Figure 106) 336FB (Figure 107) Access panel Elevator hinge 335GB (Figure 106) 336GB (Figure 107) Access panel Elevator hinge 335HB (Figure 106) 336HB (Figure 107) Access panel Elevator hinge Differential pressure switch of the horizontal stabilizer 337AZ (Figure 106) Access panel anti-icing system Differential pressure switch of the horizontal stabilizer 337BZ (Figure 106) Access panel anti-icing system 337CZ (Figure 106) Access panel - 337DL (Figure 106) Access panel Strobe light power supply [1] Aircraft with Electromechanical gust lock. 3. Location of the Access Doors and Panels A. The figures below give the location of the access doors and panels in sub-zones 310, 320 and 330 in details: (1) Figure 101 and Figure 102 - Sub-zone 310 - Fuselage Rear Section II Access Doors and Panels (2) Figure 103 - Sub-zone 320 - Vertical Stabilizer and Rudders Access Doors and Panels (LH) (3) Figure 104 - Sub-zone 320 - Vertical Stabilizer and Rudders Access Doors and Panels (RH) (4) Figure 105 - Sub-zone 320 - Tail Boom Access Doors and Panels (5) Figure 106 - Sub-zone 330 - Horizontal Stabilizer and Elevator Access Doors and Panels (LH) (6) Figure 107 - Sub-zone 330 - Horizontal Stabilizer and Elevator Access Doors and Panels (RH) EMB-145  - AMM 1285 PGBLK 100 CONFIG-1 06-42-00 Page 4 of 11 Rev 53 - Oct 31/17 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="5" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL EFFECTIVITY: VALID FOR AIRCRAFT WITHOUT APU COWLING 145-54858 SERIES Fuselage Rear Section II (Sub-zone 310) Access Doors and Panels  Figure 101 A 4 S 313 BL 313 CL 5 L 313 AL 4 S 4 S 313GR DET. A 313 ER 9 S 313 FR 5 S 313 DR 312 AR 4 S 6 C DET. A 145AMM060038.MCE B EMB-145  - AMM 1285 PGBLK 100 CONFIG-1 06-42-00 Page 5 of 11 Rev 53 - Oct 31/17 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="6" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL EFFECTIVITY: VALID FOR AIRCRAFT WITH APU COWLING 145-54858 SERIES Fuselage Rear Section II (Sub-zone 310) Access Doors and Panels  Figure 102 A 4 S 313 BL 313 CL 5 L 313 AL 4 S DET. A 313 ER 22 S 313 DR 4 S 312 AR 6 C DET. A 145AMM060336.MCE EMB-145  - AMM 1285 PGBLK 100 CONFIG-1 06-42-00 Page 6 of 11 Rev 53 - Oct 31/17 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="7" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL EFFECTIVITY: ALL Vertical Stabilizer and Rudders (Sub-zone 320) Access Doors and Panels (LH)  Figure 103 A 6 S 1 6 S 325 FL 326 HL 24 S 324 EL 15 S 325 EL 6 S 10 S 326 GL 10 S 324 DL 325 BL 10 S 11 S 324 CL 327 DL 10 S S 4 S 8 S 16 324 BL 325 DL 326 EL 325 CL 12 S S 6 326 FL 326 DL 11 S 327 CL 326 BL 11 S S 8 327 BL 322 AL 324 AL 325 AL 12 S 10 S 326 AL 7 S 22 S 326 CL 6 S DET. A 327 AL 11 S 1 APPLICABLE TO AIRCRAFT 004/999 145AMM060043.MCE B EMB-145  - AMM 1285 PGBLK 100 CONFIG-1 06-42-00 Page 7 of 11 Rev 53 - Oct 31/17 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="8" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL EFFECTIVITY: ALL Vertical Stabilizer and Rudders (Sub-zone 320) Access Doors and Panels (RH)  Figure 104 A 24 S 324 FR 9 S 10 S 325 KR 325 JR 12 S 6 S 325 LR 327 HR 10 S 325 HR 10 S 8 S 325 FR 6 S 322 BR 327 GR 10 S 325 GR 6 S 327 FR 6 S 327 ER DET. A 145AMM060044.MCE A EMB-145  - AMM 1285 PGBLK 100 CONFIG-1 06-42-00 Page 8 of 11 Rev 53 - Oct 31/17 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="9" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL EFFECTIVITY: ALL Tail Boom (Sub-zone 320) Access Doors and Panels  Figure 105 F B A ZONE 321 C D E DET. A 12S 321FL DET. B 26S 321BL DET. C 21S 321EL 26S 321AL 15S 321DR DET. F DET. E DET. D 15S 321CL 145AMM060439.MCE EMB-145  - AMM 1285 PGBLK 100 CONFIG-1 06-42-00 Page 9 of 11 Rev 53 - Oct 31/17 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="10" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL EFFECTIVITY: ALL Horizontal Stabilizer and Elevator (Sub-zone 330) Access Doors and Panels (LH)  Figure 106 A 2 2 2 12 S 14 S 8 S 337 BZ 15 S 337 CZ 337 AZ 337 DL B 334 DR 333 DL DET. A 21 S 3 321 EL 12 S 1 8 S 335 GB 8 S 8 S 8 S 335 EB 335 HB 8 S 335 FB 335 CB DET. A 12 S 335 DB 8 S 4 S 335 BB 335 AB 333 CB 10 S 333 BB 8 S 333 AB 8 S DET. B 1 APPLICABLE TO AIRCRAFT 012/999 2 APPLICABLE TO AIRCRAFT 001/038 3 EM145AMM060041E.DGN APPLICABLE TO AIRCRAFT 038/999 EMB-145  - AMM 1285 PGBLK 100 CONFIG-1 06-42-00 Page 10 of 11 Rev 53 - Oct 31/17 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="11" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL EFFECTIVITY: ALL Horizontal Stabilizer and Elevator (Sub-zone 330) Access Doors and Panels (RH)  Figure 107 A 8 S 12 S 336 EB 336 GB 8 S 8 S 8 S 336 HB 4 S 336 CB 336 FB 336 AB 12 S 8 S 336 DB 336 BB 334 CB 10 S 334 BB 8 S 334 AB 8 S DET. A EM145AMM060600A.DGN EMB-145  - AMM 1285 PGBLK 100 CONFIG-1 06-42-00 Page 11 of 11 Rev 53 - Oct 31/17 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="12" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data/>
		</page>
	</pages>
</metadata>
