<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata id="MPP1285_06-41-05-01-1">
	<file family="145" manual="AMM" pn="1285" chg="U" tsn="51" is_tr="false">
		<title>AMM PART II-1285 - CHAPTER 06-41-05-01 - BAGGAGE COMPARTMENT INTERNAL PANELS - COMPONENT LOCATION</title>
		<path>/CHAPTER_06</path>
		<hash>79decc117e35ddd46a585b2fd2b19254</hash>
	</file>
	<pages>
		<page number="1" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL BAGGAGE COMPARTMENT INTERNAL PANELS - COMPONENT LOCATION EFFECTIVITY:  ALL 1. General A. This section gives the location of the internal panels of the major zone 200 in the baggage compartment. EMB-145  - AMM 1285 General 06-41-05 Page 1 of 3 Rev 48 - Oct  30/15 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="2" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL BAGGAGE COMPARTMENT INTERNAL PANELS - COMPONENT LOCATION EFFECTIVITY:  ALL 2. List of the Equipment and Components A. Table 101 gives the equipment and components to which you can get access through the baggage compartment internal panels. Table 101 - MAJOR ZONE 200 - BAGGAGE COMPARTMENT PANEL IDENTIFICATION NUM- BER EQUIPMENT/COMPONENTS LEFT RIGHT FIG Hydraulic tubing, Engine fuel tubing, Thermoacoustic insula- 271ALW  tion Bleed tubing, Fire extinguisher tubing, Thermoacoustic insu- 271BLW  lation 271CLW Bleed tubing 271DLW Bleed tubing Hydraulic tubing, Engine fuel tubing, Thermoacoustic insula-  272ARW tion  272BRW Thermoacoustic insulation, Structure Bleed tubing, Fire extinguisher tubing, Thermoacoustic insu-  272CRW (Figure lation 101)  272DRW Bleed tubing  272ERW Bleed tubing  272FRW Baggage door Torsion bar  272GRW Baggage door Torsion bar Control cables, Hydraulic tubing, Baggage door Torsion bar, 273ATC  Thermoacoustic insulation Control cables, Hydraulic tubing, Baggage door lifting and 273BTC  lowering mechanism, Thermoacoustic insulation Control cables, Hydraulic tubing, Pulley, Thermoacoustic in- 273CTC  sulation 3. Location of the Baggage Compartment Internal Access Panels A. Figure 101 gives the location of the baggage-compartment internal access panels. EMB-145  - AMM 1285 PGBLK 100 06-41-05 Page 2 of 3 Rev 48 - Oct  30/15 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="3" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL EFFECTIVITY: ALL Baggage Compartment Internal Panels  Figure 101 A 273ATC 273BTC 273CTC 272GRW 272FRW 272ERW 271DLW 272ARW 271ALW 272BRW 272DRW 271CLW 271BLW 272CRW DET. A 145AMM060056.MCE B EMB-145  - AMM 1285 PGBLK 100 06-41-05 Page 3 of 3 Rev 48 - Oct  30/15 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="4" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data/>
		</page>
	</pages>
</metadata>
