<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<metadata id="MPP1285_49-19-02-04-1">
  <file family="145" manual="AMM" pn="1285" chg="U" tsn="51" is_tr="false">
    <title>AMM PART II-1285 - CHAPTER 49-19-02-04 - APU DRAIN SCAVENGE PUMP - REMOVAL/INSTALLATION</title>
    <path>/CHAPTER_49</path>
    <hash>a6ef6ae385ab9663274876e8f75dff89</hash>
  </file>
  <pages>
    <page number="1" width="216.0" height="279.0">
      <data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL APU DRAIN SCAVENGE PUMP - REMOVAL/INSTALLATION EFFECTIVITY:  AIRCRAFT WITH APU T-62T-40C14 1. General A. This procedure gives the instructions to remove and install the APU drain scavenge pump. B. The APU drain scavenge pump is attached to the APU cowling. C. The procedures in this section are given in the sequence below. The tasks identified with ( &#x2666;) are part of the Scheduled Maintenance Requirements Document (SMRD). TASK NUMBER DESCRIPTION EFFECTIVITY AIRCRAFT WITH APU APU DRAIN SCAVENGE PUMP - REMOV- DRAIN SCAVENGE 49-19-02-000-801-A AL PUMP   AIRCRAFT WITH APU APU DRAIN SCAVENGE PUMP - INSTAL- DRAIN SCAVENGE 49-19-02-400-801-A LATION PUMP   EMB-145  - AMM 1285 General 49-19-02 Page 1 of 6 Rev 48 - Oct  30/15 Copyright © by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
    </page>
    <page number="2" width="216.0" height="279.0">
      <data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL TASK 49-19-02-000-801-A EFFECTIVITY:  AIRCRAFT WITH APU DRAIN SCAVENGE PUMP 2. APU DRAIN SCAVENGE PUMP - REMOVAL A. General (1) This procedure gives the instructions to remove the APU drain scavenge pump. B. References REFERENCE DESIGNATION AMM MPP 49-02-00/200 - MAINTENANCE PRACTICES AMM TASK 49-15-00-000-801-A/400 APU COWLING - REMOVAL C. Zones and Accesses ZONE PANEL/DOOR LOCATION 313 APU Cowling Aircraft tail cone D. Tools and Equipment Not Applicable E. Auxiliary Items ITEM DESCRIPTION PURPOSE QTY Commercially Workstand To get access to the work area 1 available F. Consumable Materials Not Applicable G. Expandable Parts Not Applicable H. Persons Recommended QTY FUNCTION PLACE 1 Does the task Aircraft tail cone I. Preparation SUBTASK 841-002-A EFFECTIVITY: AIRCRAFT WITH APU DRAIN SCAVENGE PUMP WARNING: BEFORE YOU DO THE TASK, OBEY THE SAFETY PRECAUTIONS GIVEN IN AMM MPP 49-02-00/200 TO PREVENT INJURY TO PERSONS AND DAMAGE TO MATERIAL. (1) On the circuit breaker panel, open this circuit breakers and attach a DO-NOT-CLOSE tag to it: &#x2022; APU FUEL SOV. EMB-145  - AMM 1285 000-801-A/400 49-19-02 Page 2 of 6 Rev 48 - Oct  30/15 Copyright © by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
    </page>
    <page number="3" width="216.0" height="279.0">
      <data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL (2) On the left power control and distribution box, open the APU GEN START circuit breaker and attach a DO-NOT-CLOSE tag to it. (3) Put the work stand below the aircraft tail cone. (4) Remove the APU cowling ( AMM TASK 49-15-00-000-801-A/400). J. Removal (Figure 401)  SUBTASK 020-002-A EFFECTIVITY: AIRCRAFT WITH APU DRAIN SCAVENGE PUMP (1) Loosen the torque and disconnect the drain exit tube (2) from the APU drain scavenge pump (5). (2) Loosen the torque and disconnect the combustor drain connection tube (1) from the APU drain scavenge pump (5). (3) Put protection caps on the disconnected parts. (4) Loosen the torque and remove the nut (3) and the washer (4). (5) Remove the APU drain scavenge pump (5) from the APU cowling. EMB-145  - AMM 1285 000-801-A/400 49-19-02 Page 3 of 6 Rev 48 - Oct  30/15 Copyright © by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
    </page>
    <page number="4" width="216.0" height="279.0">
      <data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL EFFECTIVITY: AIRCRAFT WITH APU T-62T-40C14 APU Drain Scavenge Pump - Removal/Installation  Figure 401 A ZONE 313 B 1 DET. A C 1. COMBUSTOR DRAIN     CONNECTION TUBE 5. APU DRAIN      SCAVENGE PUMP 4. WASHER 3. NUT B DET. B DET. A TYPICAL 2. DRAIN EXIT C     TUBE 4 2 3 1 VALID FOR AIRCRAFT WITH APU COWLING 145-54858 SERIES. 2 5.5 ±1.5 mm TORQUE: 50.8 TO 56.5 N.m (450 TO 500 lb.in). VIEW C (0.22±0.06 in) TY