<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1"?>
<metadata id="MPP1285_27-71-12-05-1">
  <file family="145" manual="AMM" pn="1285" chg="U" tsn="51" is_tr="false">
    <title>AMM PART II-1285 - CHAPTER 27-71-12-05 - GUST LOCK COMMAND SWITCHES - ADJUSTMENT/TEST</title>
    <path>/CHAPTER_27</path>
    <hash>4c49df0c1c0bc10bd18d6037ff0f0664</hash>
  </file>
  <pages>
    <page number="1" width="216.0" height="279.0">
      <data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL GUST LOCK COMMAND SWITCHES - ADJUSTMENT/TEST EFFECTIVITY:  AIRCRAFT WITH ELECTROMECHANICAL GUST LOCK 1. General A. This section gives the procedures to do the adjustment of the gust lock command switches. B. The gust lock command switches are components of the electromechanical gust lock system. It is situated in the Engine Control Box. C. The procedures in this section are given in the sequence below. The tasks identified with ( &#x2666;) are part of the Scheduled Maintenance Requirements Document (SMRD). TASK NUMBER DESCRIPTION EFFECTIVITY AIRCRAFT WITH GUST LOCK COMMAND SWITCHES - AD- ELECTROMECHANI- 27-71-12-700-801-A JUSTMENT CAL GUST LOCK   EMB-145  - AMM 1285 General 27-71-12 Page 1 of 10 Rev 48 - Oct  30/15 Copyright © by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
    </page>
    <page number="2" width="216.0" height="279.0">
      <data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL TASK 27-71-12-700-801-A EFFECTIVITY:  AIRCRAFT WITH ELECTROMECHANICAL GUST LOCK 2. GUST LOCK COMMAND SWITCHES - ADJUSTMENT A. General (1) This task gives the procedures to do the adjustment of the gust lock command switches. B. References REFERENCE DESIGNATION AMM MPP 06-41-03/100 - COMPONENT LOCATION ENERGIZATION OF THE AIRCRAFT WITH AN EX- AMM TASK 20-40-01-860-801-A/200 TERNAL POWER SOURCE ELECTROMECHANICAL GUST LOCK - OPERATION- AMM TASK 27-71-00-700-801-A/500 AL CHECK S.B.145-27-0101 - S.B.145-27-0125 - C. Zones and Accesses ZONE PANEL/DOOR LOCATION 223 223NZ Control pedestal 223 223RZ Control pedestal D. Tools and Equipment ITEM DESCRIPTION PURPOSE QTY Commercially Analog Multimeter To do the check for electrical continuity  available Commercially Feeler Gauge To measure the gap  available E. Auxiliary Items Not Applicable F. Consumable Materials Not Applicable G. Expandable Parts Not Applicable H. Persons Recommended QTY FUNCTION PLACE 1 Does the task Cockpit EMB-145  - AMM 1285 700-801-A/500 27-71-12 Page 2 of 10 Rev 48 - Oct  30/15 Copyright © by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
    </page>
    <page number="3" width="216.0" height="279.0">
      <data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL I. Preparation SUBTASK 841-002-A (1) Make sure the gust lock lever is at locked position. (2) (For aircraft with thrust reverser) On the circuit breaker panel, open these circuit breakers and attach DO-NOT-CLOSE tags to them: &#x2022; LIGHTS - PEDESTAL PANEL. &#x2022; POWERPLANT - START 1/2. &#x2022; POWERPLANT - FADEC 1A/2A - 1B/2B. &#x2022; POWERPLANT - ELEC. IDLE STOP 1/2. &#x2022; POWERPLANT - THRUST REVERSER 1/2. &#x2022; GUST LOCK. (3) (For aircraft without thrust reverser) On the circuit breaker panel, open these circuit breakers and attach DO-NOT-CLOSE tags to them: &#x2022; LIGHTS - PEDESTAL PANEL. &#x2022; POWERPLANT - START 1/2. &#x2022; POWERPLANT - FADEC 1A/2A - 1B/2B. &#x2022; GUST LOCK. (4) Remove the screw (1) and (2) that attach the control stand mask (Figure 501). (5) Remove access panel 223RZ and 223NZ ( AMM MPP 06-41-03/100). (6) Energize the aircraft with the External DC Power Supply AMM TASK 20-40-01-860-801-A/200. J. Adjustment of the Gust Lock Command Switches SUBTASK 720-002-A (1) Do the adjustment of the gust lock command switches (Figure 502), as follows: (2) Move the gust lock lever to the intermediate position. (3) Untighten the bolts (3) from the microswitch support (2). (4) Position the support until the gap between the cam (3) and the end plunger (4) is approximately 2 millimeters long (VIEW D deactuated, Figure 502). NOTE: Use a feeler gauge to measure the gap between the cam (3) and the plunger (4). (5) Tighten the bolts (1) from the microswitch support (2) (Figure 502). (6) Move the gust lock lever to the locked position. EMB-145  - AMM 1285 700-801-A/500 27-71-12 Page 3 of 10 Rev 48 - Oct  30/15 Copyright © by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
    </page>
    <page number="4" width="216.0" height="279.0">
      <data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL (7) (For aircraft PRE-MOD. S.B.145-27-0101) Do a continuity check on the command switches: (a) Check the continuity between the pin 24 and 13 from the connector P1270. (b) Check the continuity between the pin 12 and 4 from the connector P1270. (c) Check the continuity between the pin 12 from the connector P1270 and the pin A from the connector P1269. (8) (For aircraft POST-MOD. S.B.145-27-0101) Do a continuity check on the command switches: (a) Check the continuity between the pin 24 and 13 from the connector P1270. (b) Check the continuity between the pin 12 and 4 from the connector P1270. (c) Set the Engine Thrust Levers (1 and 2) to the Idle position. (d) With the Engine Thrust Levers (1 and 2) set to the Idle position, check the continuity between the pin M (-) and pin A (+) from the connector P1269. NOTE: The polarity of the diode must be observed in the continuity check. (9) Move the gust lock lever to the intermediate position. NOTE: The sound click must be heard. (10) (For aircraft PRE-MOD. S.B.145-27-0101) Do a discontinuity check on the command switches: (a) Check the discontinuity between the pin 24 and 13 from the connector P1270. (b) Check the discontinuity between the pin 12 and 4 from the connector P1270. (c) Check the discontinuity between the pin 12 from the connector P1270 and the pin A from the connector P1269. (11) (For aircraft POST-MOD. S.B.145-27-0101) Do a discontinuity check on the command switches: (a) Check the discontinuity between the pin 24 and 13 from the connector P1270. (b) Check the discontinuit