<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata id="MPP1285_20-30-05-02-1">
	<file family="145" manual="AMM" pn="1285" chg="R" tsn="55" is_tr="false">
		<title>AMM PART II-1285 - CHAPTER 20-30-05-02 - PAINTING MATERIALS - MAINTENANCE PRACTICES</title>
		<path>/CHAPTER_20</path>
		<hash>11ea400b2a49b9a77e6d3e75c376155d</hash>
	</file>
	<pages>
		<page number="1" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL PAINTING MATERIALS - MAINTENANCE PRACTICES EFFECTIVITY: ALL 1. General A. This subchapter gives a list of the products approved to be used on, and for the servicing of, the aircraft, with their most usual suppliers. B. The correct procedure to use the products must be referred to in the chapters given in the table. C. Products with the same specification MIL-, FED. SPEC., but of different makes, must not be mixed. D. Possible alternative products are opposite the same group of chapters where the indicated product(s) is(are) referred to. E. Products given on the QPL (Qualified Products List) for specifications MIL referred to in this subchapter are automatically approved to be used on the aircraft. F. The supplier/manufacturer addresses are given in section AMM MPP 20-30-00/200. EMB-145  - AMM 1285 General 20-30-05 Page 1 of 5 Rev 55 - Oct 29/18 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="2" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL PAINTING MATERIALS - MAINTENANCE PRACTICES EFFECTIVITY: ALL 2. List of the Products Approved to be Used on the Aircraft A. This table gives the Painting Materials approved to be used on the aircraft. Table 201 - PAINTING MATERIALS TO USE, REFER TO MAINTENANCE COMMERCIAL PROD- SUPPLIER/MANUFAC- SPECIFICATION MANUAL INDICA- UCT TURER TION OR SERVICE BULLETIN Alodine 1200S 26-21-02 27-20-00 BONDERITE M-CR 1200 28-11-00 S AERO Class 1A 28-21-01 BONDERITE M-CR 1200 31-11-01 S AERO Class 3 31-12-01 BONDERITE M-CR 31-14-01 MIL-C-5541 11132 AERO 31-16-01 MIL-C-81706 Henkel 34-32-08 MIL-DTL-81706 34-42-01 38-33-05 51-80-02 53-01-05 Alodine 1201 53-21-05 53-21-06 53-21-07 71-12-02 Alodine 1200 MIL-C-81706 Henkel 25-11-01 BONDERITE M-CR 1200 S AERO Acrylic Nitrocellulose 20-10-10 MIL-L-19538 Local Supplier Gloss Lacquer 53-12-01 24-34-05 31-11-01 31-12-01 Nylon Varnish, Fluid-Re- 31-14-01 MEP 10-057 sistant Nycote 31-16-01 Nycote 7-11-Dark Blue 34-32-09 34-32-10 34-32-12 34-42-01 [1] The color is specified according to the aircraft configuration. EMB-145  - AMM 1285 PGBLK 200 20-30-05 Page 2 of 5 Rev 55 - Oct 29/18 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="3" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL Table 201 - PAINTING MATERIALS (Continued) TO USE, REFER TO MAINTENANCE COMMERCIAL PROD- SUPPLIER/MANUFAC- SPECIFICATION MANUAL INDICA- UCT TURER TION OR SERVICE BULLETIN Nylon Varnish, Fluid-Re- MEP 10-057 sistant Nycote Nycote 7-11-Dark Blue 20-13-21 Coating, HS Polyur- MEP 10-069 ethane, Blue PRC Desoto International Ref PMS 654C Alexit FST Fullgrund - 343-55 Alexit FST Hartner - 345-15 Mankiewicz Gebr. &amp; Co. 25-00-00 Alexit FST Strukturlack - 346-65 Alexit FST Hartner - 345-19 - WLS 982-1428 WLS Coatings 25-00-00 WLS 412 - (1 part) -109 Inspection Torque Seal 23-31-00 MEP 09-068 F925 - Pink - Torque Organic Products Co. 53-12-01 Seal 73-22-01 Antibiological Compound (Fuel Tank Coating) Base-825/309, activator: PRC DESOTO 910/702, and reducer: 020/707 AR Antibiological Compound (Fuel Tank Coating) Base: 20P1-10, catalyst: PC-108, and solvent: AMS-C-27725 Akzo Nobel 28-11-00 TR-53 Type II Antibiological Compound (Fuel Tank Coating) 20P1-21/K1G Antibiological Compound (Fuel Tank Coating) Base: FT-9-Y1, harden- Axon Aerospace Inc. er: PH-24, and reducer: SR-25 [1] The color is specified according to the aircraft configuration. EMB-145  - AMM 1285 PGBLK 200 20-30-05 Page 3 of 5 Rev 55 - Oct 29/18 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="4" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL Table 201 - PAINTING MATERIALS (Continued) TO USE, REFER TO MAINTENANCE COMMERCIAL PROD- SUPPLIER/MANUFAC- SPECIFICATION MANUAL INDICA- UCT TURER TION OR SERVICE BULLETIN Paint Stripper SOCO- STRIP A0103N SOCOMOR (Hydrogen Peroxide MEP 21-016 Base) AMS 1375B Paint Stripper PR-3500 Eldorado Solutions 23-60-01 (Phenol Base) MIL-R-81903 Paint Stripper PR-2002 Eldorado Solutions AMS 1376 (Acid Base) Paint Stripper PR-5044 - Eldorado Solutions (Peroxide Base) Paint Stripper SOCO- STRIP A0103N SOCOMOR MEP 21-016 28-11-00 (Hydrogen Peroxide AMS 1375B 28-21-01 Base) Dasic D 23 Dasic International Ltd Epoxy Primer for Struc- tural Parts Akzo Nobel 10-P4-2/EC-117 MEP 10-059 51-21-02 Epoxy Primer for Struc- tural Parts PRC DeSoto 515K011/910-012 High Solids Epoxy Pri- mer for Exterior MEP 10-068 Akzo Nobel 51-21-02 10-P20-44/EC-265/ TR114 Conventional Polyur- 25-12-09 MEP 10-069 ethane Coating Akzo Nobel 51-21-02 MIL-PRF-85285 (24 F2 Series) 52-00-00 FT201-1 Temporary Protective Coating for Skin Quality MEP 13-060 Aztec Sheet (AZ 644) 10-10-02 Temporary Protective Coating for Skin Quality - Groco Specialty Coatings Sheet (989-0016) Clear Gloss Polyur- Akzo Nobel 20-12-01 MEP 10-058 ethane Varnish Axon Aerospace, Inc 32-10-09 15200 Blue Acrylic Lac- Tecno Quimica S.A. 10-047 CMM 21-25-01 quer Paint Interturbine Logistik [1] The color is specified according to the aircraft configuration. EMB-145  - AMM 1285 PGBLK 200 20-30-05 Page 4 of 5 Rev 55 - Oct 29/18 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="5" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL Table 201 - PAINTING MATERIALS (Continued) TO USE, REFER TO MAINTENANCE COMMERCIAL PROD- SUPPLIER/MANUFAC- SPECIFICATION MANUAL INDICA- UCT TURER TION OR SERVICE BULLETIN Paint Polyurethane Wa- ter Base for Interior MEP 10-073 HSH Aerospace (I) 25-13-00 Series IP 1083 FED. STD 595-36173 Green Epoxy Primer EMBRAER GPX LTDA (17084GEP-LVOC/ HENTZEN COATINGS, 17085CEH-LVOC) INC. MEP 10-069 35-11-03 High Solids Polyurethane Green Paint EMBRAER GPX LTDA (PE54004GNGL0007) [1] The color is specified according to the aircraft configuration. EMB-145  - AMM 1285 PGBLK 200 20-30-05 Page 5 of 5 Rev 55 - Oct 29/18 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="6" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data/>
		</page>
	</pages>
</metadata>
