<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata id="MPP1285_20-30-01-02-1">
	<file family="145" manual="AMM" pn="1285" chg="R" tsn="54" is_tr="false">
		<title>AMM PART II-1285 - CHAPTER 20-30-01-02 - FUEL AND SERVICE FLUIDS - MAINTENANCE PRACTICES</title>
		<path>/CHAPTER_20</path>
		<hash>928913ca3eeb82f8cca3d8f295952eac</hash>
	</file>
	<pages>
		<page number="1" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL FUEL AND SERVICE FLUIDS - MAINTENANCE PRACTICES EFFECTIVITY: ALL 1. General A. This subchapter gives a list of the products approved to be used on, and for the servicing of, the aircraft, with their most usual suppliers. B. The correct procedure to use the products, and for filling, charging, or other applications is given in the chapters referred to below. C. Fuels with the same specification MIL-, FED. SPEC., but of different makes, can be mixed. D. Products listed on the QPL (Qualified Products List) for MIL specifications, referred to in this subchapter, are automatically approved to be used on the aircraft. E. Possible alternative products are listed opposite to the same group of chapters where the indicated product(s) is(are) referenced to. F. All Phosphate Ester-Base Hydraulic Fluid Type IV are miscible and compatible and may be used with each other in any and all proportions. G. The supplier/manufacturer addresses are listed in the section AMM MPP 20-30-00/200. EMB-145  - AMM 1285 General 20-30-01 Page 1 of 3 Rev 54 - Apr 27/18 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="2" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL FUEL AND SERVICE FLUIDS - MAINTENANCE PRACTICES EFFECTIVITY: ALL 2. List of the Products Approved to be Used on the aircraft A. The table below gives the Engine Fuel and Servicing Fluids approved to be used on the aircraft. Table 201 - ENGINE FUEL TO USE, REFER TO COMMERCIAL PROD- SPECIFICATION SUPPLIER/MANUFACTURER MAINTENANCE UCT MANUAL INDICATION 12-11-01 CNP-08 QAV1 Local Supplier 12-11-02 JET A 12-11-01 ASTM D1655 Local Supplier JET A-1 12-11-02 12-11-01 MIL-T83133A JP8 Local Supplier 12-11-02 12-11-01 GB 6537-94 No. 3 Jet Fuel Local Supplier 12-11-02 12-11-01 GOST 10227-86 TS-1 Local Supplier 12-11-02 12-11-01 MIL-T-5624L JP5 Local Supplier 12-11-02 [1] The list contains optional fuels that cannot be applicable to a specific aircraft serial number. Refer to the latest revision of the AFM for the list of approved ones. Table 202 - SERVICING FLUIDS TO USE, REFER TO COMMERCIAL PROD- SPECIFICATION SUPPLIER/MANUFACTURER MAINTENANCE UCT MANUAL INDICATION MIL-PRF-5606 Hydraulic Fluid or Shell 27-51-00 (Aeroshell Fluid 4 or 41) MIL-H-5606 MIL-PRF-5606 Hydraulic Fluid 32-10-02 or As per MIL-PRF-5606 Local Supplier 32-20-01 MIL-H-5606 requirements 32-20-08 12-13-06 21-31-13 32-10-02 FED. SPEC. 32-20-01 BB-N-411 32-44-02 superseded by Nitrogen Local Supplier 32-49-01 A-A-59503 32-49-04 Type I, Class I, 34-13-00 Grade B 35-10-00 35-10-04 35-11-02 MIL-O-27210 Oxygen Local Supplier 12-14-00 [1] EMBRAER-CMM task. EMB-145  - AMM 1285 PGBLK 200 20-30-01 Page 2 of 3 Rev 54 - Apr 27/18 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="3" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL Table 202 - SERVICING FLUIDS (Continued) TO USE, REFER TO COMMERCIAL PROD- SPECIFICATION SUPPLIER/MANUFACTURER MAINTENANCE UCT MANUAL INDICATION Phosphate Ester-Base 12-13-01 Hydraulic Fluid Solutia 20-10-06 (Skydrol 500B-4) Phosphate Ester-Base SAE AS 1241, 12-13-01 Hydraulic Fluid Solutia Type IV 20-10-06 (Skydrol LD-4) Phosphate Ester-Base 12-13-01 Hydraulic Fluid Exxon 20-10-06 ( HyJet IV-A plus) WILLIAMS REFRIGERATION HFC R134A Service Fluids 21-52-00FT501-1 LTD [1] EMBRAER-CMM task. EMB-145  - AMM 1285 PGBLK 200 20-30-01 Page 3 of 3 Rev 54 - Apr 27/18 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="4" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data/>
		</page>
	</pages>
</metadata>
