<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<metadata id="MPP1285_20-10-05-02-1">
	<file family="145" manual="AMM" pn="1285" chg="U" tsn="51" is_tr="false">
		<title>AMM PART II-1285 - CHAPTER 20-10-05-02 - JAMMED SCREWS - MAINTENANCE PRACTICES</title>
		<path>/CHAPTER_20</path>
		<hash>ceff18e20feff7ba5eac00aa28e9895a</hash>
	</file>
	<pages>
		<page number="1" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL JAMMED SCREWS - MAINTENANCE PRACTICES EFFECTIVITY:  ALL 1. General A. This procedure shows how to use a special tool that permits you to remove caught screws which you cannot remove with the usual impact wrenches. EMB-145  - AMM 1285 General 20-10-05 Page 1 of 3 Rev 48 - Oct  30/15 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="2" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL JAMMED SCREWS - MAINTENANCE PRACTICES EFFECTIVITY:  ALL 2. Equipment A. GSE 035 - ExtractorTo remove stuck screws 3. Typical Removal Procedure (Figure 201) A. Loosen a screw adjacent to the caught screw, as necessary, to permit the tool to be correctly installed and held. NOTE: If the loosened screw does not permit the tool attachment, replace the screw temporarily. B. Put the tool holding point on the loosened screw. C. Install a bit of the correct size for the type of the related screw to the tool sliding support adapter. D. Install the bit to the related screw and push with the tool handle. E. Install a flex handle to the sliding support adapter and remove the screw. F. Examine the body of the loosened screw and, if necessary, replace the screw. EMB-145  - AMM 1285 PGBLK 200 20-10-05 Page 2 of 3 Rev 48 - Oct  30/15 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="3" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data>AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE MANUAL EFFECTIVITY: ALL Typical Removal of Caught Screws  Figure 201 145AMM200041.MCE EMB-145  - AMM 1285 PGBLK 200 20-10-05 Page 3 of 3 Rev 48 - Oct  30/15 Copyright Â© by Embraer S.A. All rights reserved - See title page for details.</data>
		</page>
		<page number="4" width="216.0" height="279.0">
			<data/>
		</page>
	</pages>
</metadata>
